[
  [
    "E L M A J O Y 😁\n",
    [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ],
    0
  ],
  [
    "@pheebinthebox //BRUH// I LO VE IT\n",
    [
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "E-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ],
    2
  ],
  [
    "never shopped at Victoria secret before but I'm making purchases ya know ya know\n",
    [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-ORG",
      "I-ORG",
      "I-ORG",
      "I-ORG",
      "I-ORG",
      "I-ORG",
      "I-ORG",
      "I-ORG",
      "I-ORG",
      "I-ORG",
      "I-ORG",
      "I-ORG",
      "I-ORG",
      "I-ORG",
      "E-ORG",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O"
    ],
    15
  ],
  [
    "Still up waiting 4 Andy #Murray v @GrigorDimitrov night match @AustralianOpen! But in my case its 430 AM EST lol #sleepisfortheweak #AusOpen\n",
    [
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "E-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "E-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "I-PER",
      "E-PER",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-MISC",
      "I-MISC",
      "I-MISC",
      "I-MISC",
      "I-MISC",
      "I-MISC",
      "I-MISC",
      "I-MISC",
      "I-MISC",
      "I-MISC",
      "I-MISC",
      "I-MISC",
      "I-MISC",
      "E-MISC",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "O",
      "B-MISC",
      "I-MISC",
      "I-MISC",
      "I-MISC",
      "I-MISC",
      "I-MISC",
      "E-MISC",
      "O"
    ],
    3
  ]
]