E NN O
L NN O
M NN O
A DT O
J NN O
O NN O
Y NN O
😁 NN O

@pheebinthebox JJ B-PER
//BRUH// NN O
I PRP O
LO NNP O
VE NNP O
IT PRP O

Still NNP O
up JJ O
waiting IN O
4 CD O
Andy DT B-PER
#Murray # B-PER
v NN O
@GrigorDimitrov NN B-PER
night NN O
match VB O
@AustralianOpen VB B-MISC
But NNP O
in NN O
my NN O
case VB O
its NN O
430 CD O
AM DT O
EST NNP O
lol NN O
#sleepisfortheweak # O
#AusOpen # B-MISC

@Albondiga94 VB B-PER
gt NN O
or NN O
v6 NN O

I PRP O
made VB O
it NN O
to NN O
100 CD O
followers JJ O

Yum NNP O
done NN O
right NN O
at DT O
@PhilzCoffee JJ B-ORG
in NN O
San VB B-LOC
Jose NNP I-LOC
CA VB I-LOC
https//tco/yKXZG5tk3Z NN O

@CaprisunStraw JJ B-PER
Yes NNP O
it NN O
was VB O

never JJ O
shopped NN O
at DT O
Victoria NNP B-ORG
secret NN I-ORG
before NN O
but NN O
I'm PRP O
making NN O
purchases NN O
ya NN O
know NN O
ya NN O
know NN O

@tiinoush JJ O
pay VB O
attention DT O
to NN O
how NN O
people NN O
act DT O
when NN O
you're NN O
not JJ O
on NN O
good NN O
terms NN O
true NN O
colors NNS O
will NN O
always DT O
reveal NN O
themselves NN O
#fact # O

Coulda NNP O
fucked JJ O
both NN O
yall VB O
one JJ O
of NN O
yall VB O
sucked NN O
my NN O
dick NN O
guess NN O
you NN O
can VB O
say VB O
i NN O
just NN O
came VB O
in NN O
the NN O
family VB O

I PRP O
have VB O
a DT O
huge NN O
bed NN O
and DT O
my NN O
dog NN O
takes VB O
up JJ O
more NN O
than NN O
half VB O
of NN O
it NN O

Old NNP O
3-6 LS B-MISC
Mafia NNP I-MISC
makes NN O
🎶🎤😁 JJ O

sometimes NN O
I PRP O
actually DT O
miss NN O
those NN O
immanuel JJ O
dayzzz VB O

There's NNP O
a DT O
lot NN O
more NN O
to NN O
do NN O
than NN O
I PRP O
think NN O
she NN O
realizes NN O

@SMACKHighNY JJ B-PER
#SmackShowDown # O
Who NNP O
has VB O
a DT O
better NN O
student NN O
section NN O
RT NNP O
for NN O
Red NNP B-ORG
Hook NNP I-ORG
Fav NNP O
for NN O
Highland NNP B-ORG
http//tco/WZ5KM7mX1R NN O

It PRP O
don't NN O
really NN O
matter VB O
cause VB O
I PRP O
got NN O
plans NN O
to NN O
get NN O
to NN O
know NN O
you NN O
better NN O

bumming NN O
it NN O
is NN O
the NN O
stupidest NN O
term NN O
ever NN O
cause VB O
not JJ O
once JJ O
in NN O
my NN O
life NN O
has VB O
anyone DT O
ever NN O
said VB O
that NN O
and DT O
actually DT O
looked NN O
anything DT O
like NN O
a DT O
bum NN O

@DlSNEY_QUOTE JJ O
I PRP O
loved NN O
you NN O
yesterday NN O
I PRP O
love NN O
you NN O
still JJ O
I PRP O
always DT O
have VB O
I PRP O
always DT O
will NN O
- : O
Minnie NNP B-PER
Mouse NNP I-PER
@gwc12 JJ B-PER

@abercrombie_32 VB B-PER
I'm PRP O
actually DT O
dating VB O
this NN O
girl NN O
Charity NNP O
🙌 NN O

TRAFFIC NNP O
STOP NNP O
at DT O
NE NNP B-LOC
GLISAN NNP I-LOC
ST NNP I-LOC
/ NN I-LOC
NE NNP I-LOC
223RD CD I-LOC
AVE DT I-LOC
GRESHAM NNP I-LOC
OR NNP I-LOC
Gresham NNP B-ORG
Police NNP I-ORG
#PG15000004822 # O
0144 CD O
#pdx911 # O

I PRP O
don't NN O
know NN O
but NN O
my NN O
nigga NN O
@alexecantu98 VB B-PER
was VB O
going NN O
off JJ O
last NN O
night NN O
🔥 NN O

@DaRaiderz4life NN B-PER
@RellzRantz JJ B-PER
that NN O
offer JJ O
good NN O
pay VB O
for NN O
the NN O
work NN O

Winter NNP O
carnival VB O
this NN O
weekend NN O
is NN O
going NN O
to NN O
be NN O
such NN O
a DT O
good NN O
get NN O
away DT O
💗 NN O

Luongo NNP B-PER
flashing NN O
the NN O
leather NN O

https//tco/D1PBDI0h8G NN O
@neishaseiko JJ B-PER
they NN O
stole NN O
our NN O
fucking JJ O
handshake VB O

@_arielrechelle NN B-PER
@MarilynMonroeDC JJ B-PER
One NNP O
of NN O
the NN O
worst NN O
things NN O
that NN O
could NNS O
happen😩😣👏 VB O
http//tco/IiYRT5Ja3Q NN O

never JJ O
see NN O
tomorrow NN O

@dlh___ JJ B-PER
TBH NNP O

Good NNP O
practice NN O
tonight NN O
guys NN O
ily😘❤️ NN O

@CuocoSweeting JJ B-PER
~EllenEvanEveEvelynEdwinEdithEdwardEddieEllieEllaEmilyEmmaEdnaEthelEttaElsaEldridgeErinEsterEzra JJ B-PER

New NNP B-LOC
York NNP I-LOC
is NN O
My NNP O
New NNP O
Chapter NNP O
http//tco/75m0y2ZP3D NN O

First NNP O
Joni NNP B-ORG
NehRita NNP I-ORG
Quintet NNP I-ORG
rehearsal NN O
of NN O
2015 CD O
was VB O
good NN O
We NNP O
play NN O
a DT O
noon JJ O
hr NN O
concert NNS O
@ NN O
U NN B-LOC
of NN I-LOC
G NN I-LOC
on NN O
Feb NNP O
5th CD O

My NNP O
creed NNS O
and DT O
my NN O
prayer NN O
every NN O
game VB O

@SoReIatable JJ O
Ask DT O
me NN O
with NN O
food JJ O
so NN O
I PRP O
know NN O
it's JJ O
real NN O
😋🙌 NN O
http//tco/WnlEScnJtw NN O
the NN O
forth NN O
one JJ O
@SammyLOX_ NN B-PER

Lil NNP O
bra NN O
blowing NN O
mops NN O
don't NN O
get NN O
whiped NN O

Jah NNP O
bless NN O

just NN O
got NN O
up JJ O
from JJ O
a DT O
good NN O
ass DT O
nap😩 RB O

@ThatGreekLeo JJ B-PER
can't😂 VB O

Beal NNP B-PER
took NN O
a DT O
3 CD O
in NN O
other JJ O
words NN O
the NN O
solar NN O
eclipse NN O
came VB O

I'm PRP O
sleepyyy NN O
and DT O
need JJ O
to NN O
finish NN O
this NN O
math VB O

@kelleybra JJ B-PER
Ahhhhh DT O
@nickjonas JJ B-PER
you NN O
can VB O
put NN O
me NN O
in NN O
chains NNS O
#MissUniverse # B-MISC
amennnnnnnnnnnn DT O
🙌😅 NN O

Ohhhhh NNP O
man VB O
I PRP O
took NN O
a DT O
nap RB O
and DT O
wow NN O

Slow NNP O
jams NN O
and DT O
studying NN O
consist NNS O
of NN O
my NN O
night NN O

A DT O
sister NN O
is NN O
a DT O
forever NN O
friend JJ O
💕 NN O
@ NN O
Formal NNP O
Chapter NNP O
📚 NN O
http//tco/B9A6900IRQ NN O

@Bella_0915 NN B-PER
welcome NN O
bby NN O
be NN O
careful VB O
and DT O
take VB O
care VB O
-} : O

Big NNP O
4th CD O
quarter NN O
helps NN O
Pacers VB B-ORG
end NN O
skid JJ O
down NN O
Magic NNP B-ORG
106-99 CD O
David NNP B-PER
West NNP I-PER
had VB O
20 CD O
points NN O
reserve NN O
Damjan NNP B-PER
Rudez NNP I-PER
added DT O
a… DT O
http//tco/UVaCy91KJc NN O

Idgaf PRP O
x NN O
@Jacquees JJ B-PER

@wenzelalexis47 JJ B-PER
I PRP O
miss NN O
u NN O
too NN O
boo NN O
I'll PRP O
be NN O
back VB O
soon NN O

Sunrise NNP O
Senior NNP O
Living NNP O
Activities DT O
Assistant- DT O
Part VB O
Time NNP O
#PlayaVista # B-LOC
CA VB I-LOC
http//tco/IcjGGXBOKj NN O
#Hospitality # O
#Job # O
#Jobs # O

Nigga NNP O
you NN O
daumb VB O

*gets JJ O
up JJ O
at DT O
420 CD O
every NN O
morning NN O
to NN O
smoke JJ O
a DT O
blunt* NN O

love NN O
hate VB O
thing NN O
when NN O
it NN O
comes NNS O
2 CD O
working NN O
with NN O
my NN O
ole JJ O
man VB O

@NaeGotSTAAACKS NN B-PER
Asked DT O
her NN O
what's NN O
so NN O
special NN O
about DT O
me NN O
& CC O
she NN O
tells NN O
me NN O
this😩💜 NN O
http//tco/R2vMwZ5UBo NN O
damn VB O
😩 NN O

@Kourt_Nicole0 JJ B-PER
lol NN O
aye DT O
not JJ O
to NN O
much NN O
I PRP O
don't NN O
wanna VB O
have VB O
to NN O
fire NN O
you NN O
up JJ O
on NN O
social NN O
media NN O
🌚 NN O

Graphic NNP O
Design NNP O
Aspects DT O
Retro NNP O
Girl NNP O
http//tco/Da7EIHcQhC NN O

#HelloFuture # O
My NNP O
12 CD O
year NN O
old JJ O
McCallans NNP B-MISC
is NN O
in NN O
the NN O
barrels NN O
now JJ O
Hope NNP O
to NN O
see NN O
in NN O
my NN O
glass NN O
in NN O
the NN O
future JJ O

@__kawanashena JJ B-PER
lol NN O
no NNS O
Isis PRP O
ur JJ O
classmate NNS O
was VB O
telling NN O
me NN O
about DT O
it NN O

@EXOTICBEAUTYJ JJ B-PER
hmm NN O

@Po0ch JJ B-PER
that NN O
was VB O
a DT O
joke NN O
my NN O
mouths NN O
reay NN O
numb JJ O
but NN O
i NN O
dont NN O
even NN O
got NN O
my NN O
cleats NNS O
bro NN O
 NN O

I'd PRP O
anyone DT O
is NN O
wondering NN O
my NN O
birthday NN O
is NN O
in NN O
6 CD O
days VB O
🙋 NN O

@bayernoatcake1 NN B-PER
nah RB O
the NN O
VR NNP O
troopers NN O

That NNP O
moment NN O
when NN O
you NN O
in NN O
a DT O
public NN O
place NN O
and DT O
you NN O
have VB O
to NN O
fart VB O
😂 NN O

It's PRP O
killing NN O
me NN O
seeing NN O
you NN O
everyday NN O
and DT O
acting DT O
like NN O
we NN O
were NN O
never JJ O
anything DT O

I'm PRP O
just NN O
really NN O
over JJ O
school JJ O
😩 NN O

could've NNS O
walked VB O
away DT O
but NN O
you're NN O
still JJ O
here NN O
and DT O
I'm PRP O
still JJ O
here NN O

Classic NNP O
lecture NN O
from JJ O
the NN O
legendary NN O
@WBrettWilson NN B-PER
@haskayneschool NN B-ORG
#handsonbusiness # O

My NNP O
whole NN O
timeline NN O
is NN O
full JJ O
of NN O
college NNS O
students NN O
complaining NNS O
about DT O
classes NNS O
starting NN O
back VB O
today NN O
😒 NN O
drop NN O
out JJ O
if NN O
its NN O
that NN O
bad VB O

He NNP O
got NN O
curb NNS O
stomped NN O
and DT O
didnt NN O
want VB O
it NN O
anymore DT O
💀 NN O

naps RB O
are DT O
love NN O

Making NNP O
scallop JJ O
potatoes NN O
and DT O
cheese NNS O
burgers NN O
for NN O
dinner NN O
#Yummy # O

@Sex_and_candy88 JJ B-PER
@jenaymarieee JJ B-PER
@iloveangiebello NN B-PER
party NN O
at DT O
my NN O
crib JJ O

@jawagner913 JJ B-PER
I PRP O
mean NN O
he NN O
might NN O
be NN O
cute NNS O
but NN O
he NN O
would NN O
get NN O
chipotle JJ B-ORG
http//tco/9bkGYjIYEI NN O

Can't VB O
wait IN O

All DT O
these NN O
couples NNS O
on NN O
Instagram PRP B-ORG
and DT O
I'm PRP O
here NN O
like NN O
🙎 NN O

Oh NNP O
http//tco/y99pehhT5I NN O

brazzersofficial NN O
team NN O
riders NN O
@ NN O
Northstar NNP B-LOC
California VB I-LOC
Resort NNP I-LOC
http//tco/QtlIwUSaCa NN O

Wait IN O
so NN O
because NN O
Keke NNP B-PER
Palmer VB I-PER
isn't NN O
wearing NN O
makeup NN O
and DT O
got NN O
a DT O
couple NNS O
of NN O
piercings NN O
she's NN O
ugly JJ O
I'm PRP O
confused NNS O

Tired NN O
of NN O
dealing NN O
with NN O
judgemental NN O
ass DT O
people NN O
✊💯💯 JJ O

I'm PRP O
obsessed NN O
with NN O
hoodies NN O
now JJ O
like NN O
that's NN O
all DT O
I PRP O
want VB O
to NN O
put NN O
on NN O

@Nick_Brown87 JJ B-PER
I PRP O
don't NN O
wanna VB O
be NN O
the NN O
bad VB O
luck NN O
charm NNS O
only JJ O
thing NN O
holding NN O
me NN O
back VB O

@_Massolena JJ B-PER
what NN O
is NN O
this NN O
I PRP O
hear NN O
about DT O
a DT O
change NNS O
of NN O
schools JJ O
👀 NN O

@ARichmo13 VB B-PER
just NN O
me NN O
and DT O
you NN O
prolly NN O
boo NN O
lol NN O
@yousay90 JJ B-PER
is NN O
going NN O
too NN O
So NNP O
I'll PRP O
prob NN O
hang VB O
with NN O
him NN O

I'm PRP O
going NN O
to NN O
make NN O
your NN O
life NN O
a DT O
living NN O
hell NN O

Try NNP O
& CC O
touch NN O
him NN O
again DT O
hoe NN O
I PRP O
dare VB O
you NN O
😂👏 NN O

Just NNP O
unfollowed JJ O
TF NNP B-MISC
outta JJ O
@TakeamEasy NN O
💀 NN O

@YungNilla JJ B-PER
@mattmanrx99 JJ B-PER
@NotBryceGrantz JJ B-PER
@FukieBukie JJ B-PER
I PRP O
tripped NN O
for NN O
12 CD O
hours NN O
I PRP O
gotta NN O
tell NN O
you NN O
that NN O
story NN O
one JJ O
day VB O

@BuzzFeed NN B-ORG
#cutestpuppy # O
orrrrrr NN O
#grumpiestpuppy # O
http//tco/u5jZ0TeeQP NN O

@StatikSelekt JJ B-PER
LMFAO NNP O
at DT O
the NN O
Facebook NNP B-ORG
and DT O
Insta PRP B-ORG
tweet NN O

ITS PRP O
SO NNP O
COLD NNP O
😭 NN O

All DT O
night NN O
flight JJ O
on NN O
that NN O
Madden NNP O

I PRP O
never JJ O
eat VB O
breakfast NN O

Not NNP O
seeing NN O
the NN O
18 CD O
inches NN O
of NN O
snow NN O
we NN O
were NN O
supposed NN O
to NN O
get NN O
😰😭 NN O

purple NN B-MISC
gobling NN I-MISC
http//tco/6S8Fh6Js5g NN O
#goblinweek # O
http//tco/kt3OyL4ai6 NN O

fuck JJ O
I PRP O
forgot NN O
to NN O
go NN O
get NN O
a DT O
free JJ O
chipotle JJ B-ORG
burrito NN O
yesterday😔 NN O

@cbfmcknight JJ B-PER
@DeanGilkerson JJ B-PER
You NNP O
guy's NN O
lift NN O
me NN O
up JJ O
and DT O
I PRP O
know NN O
each VB O
one JJ O
of NN O
you NN O
in NN O
my NN O
heart NN O

@ManCanddyPics JJ B-PER
Please NNP O
arrest DT O
me NN O
http//tco/MFtuIf7Uyb NN O

If PRP O
you NN O
don't NN O
want VB O
her NN O
with NN O
nobody JJ O
else NN O
then NN O
treat NN O
her NN O
like NN O
nobody JJ O
else NN O
😪 NN O

Kim NNP B-PER
You NNP O
Know NNP O
What NNP O
😂 NN O
https//tco/yiQj61luNPl NN O

Sophmores NNP O
need JJ O
to NN O
chill JJ O

@itscoleharmon NN B-PER
Today NNP O
@Snapchat JJ B-ORG
updated JJ O
so NN O
now JJ O
my NN O
girl NN O
can't VB O
see NN O
my NN O
top NN O
friends JJ O
no NNS O
more NN O
God NNP O
is NN O
great NN O
🙌😂😂😂 JJ O

@craig_movern NN O
it NN O
is NN O
lol NN O
it's JJ O
three NN O
something NN O

@Misty_Gates JJ B-PER
what's NN O
the NN O
best NN O
organism JJ O
you NN O
have VB O
ever NN O
had VB O
With NNP O
a DT O
man VB O
woman NN O
or NN O
by NN O
urself JJ O

I PRP O
graduated NN O
from JJ O
the NN O
streets NN O
no NNS O
diploma NN O

eating VB O
lunch NN O
next JJ O
to NN O
Matt NNP B-PER
Damon NNP I-PER
#casuallycasual # O

Pursuing NNP O
and DT O
protecting NN O
autonomy DT O
can VB O
be NN O
a DT O
full-time JJ O
job NN O
-> : O
@tkraz NN O
#edchat # O

Jesus NNP O

@Lilyyylyy JJ B-PER
I'm PRP O
gonna NN O
scream NN O
I PRP O
just NN O
know NN O
it NN O
lol NN O

I'm PRP O
dead NN O
😂 NN O
http//tco/mB5Czj1k8f NN O

@OnofrioModugno JJ O
🙌🙌🙌🙌🙌🙌 JJ O

@jesss_shirley JJ B-PER
Jess NNP B-PER
my NN O
story NN O
was VB O
great NN O

@lifetimetv JJ B-ORG
Catherine VB B-PER
is NN O
such NN O
a DT O
sore NN O
loser NN O
keep NN O
the NN O
camera VB O
off JJ O
her NN O
face VB O

What NNP O
you NN O
should NN O
doSince NN O
we NN O
both NN O
bored NN O
lol NN O
scGoldkidgorever JJ O
http//tco/bSUXZXZJwF NN O

On NNP O
'Endless POS B-MISC
Love' NNP I-MISC
Boys NNP O
aren't DT O
like NN O
this NN O
Boys NNP O
don't NN O
not JJ O
suck NN O
in NN O
real NN O
life NN O

@YanCarioti NN B-PER
say VB O
those NN O
three NN O
little NN O
words NN O
and DT O
its NN O
a DT O
deal NN O

Bad IN O
bitch NN O

DLee NNP B-PER
ballin VB O

I PRP O
b NN O
lazy NN O
though NN O
😴 NN O

#Minorista # O
#Trabajo # O
alerta DT O
Assistant DT O
Store NNP O
Manager NNP O
- : O
Full NNP O
Time NNP O
| NN O
Puerto NNP B-LOC
Rico NN I-LOC
| NN O
#Mayaguez # B-LOC
http//tco/3POposeN3q NN O
#Trabajos # B-ORG

Searching NNP O
for NN O
my NN O
dog NN O
this NN O
early VB O
in NN O
-6 : O
degree NN O
weather NN O
gotta NN O
love NN O
it NN O

Store NNP O
don't NN O
open JJ O
till NN O
11 CD O
😪 NN O

Goodmorning NNP O
✌️✌️ JJ O

This NNP O
is NN O
not JJ O
a DT O
semester NN O
I PRP O
can VB O
afford DT O
to NN O
be NN O
sick NN O
and DT O
I'm PRP O
sick NN O
so NN O
that's NN O
perfect NN O
😊 NN O

Watching WRB O
SOA NNP B-MISC
has VB O
me NN O
paranoid NN O
about DT O
cars VB O
pulling NN O
up JJ O
behind NN O
and DT O
beside NN O
me NN O
at DT O
the NN O
same VB O
time NN O
😂 NN O

So NNP O
BCIS NNP O
/ NN O

Dominican NNP B-LOC
is NN O
in NN O
sight NN O
🙌🌴 NN O
#missionstrip # O
#needtobetherenow # O
http//tco/pQ81PuOOc8 NN O

He NNP O
has VB O
his NN O
angles DT O
down NN O
like NN O
Pythagoras NNP B-PER
😭😭😭 JJ O

❄️☀️⛄️💙 JJ O
❄️ NN O
#EmpireStateBuilding # B-LOC
#NewYorkCity # B-LOC
@ NN O
Eataly VB B-ORG
NYC NNP O
http//tco/hnBvvF17hT NN O

@MarkTAckerman JJ B-PER
we NN O
have VB O
that NN O
effect NN O
on NN O
people NN O
- : O

First NNP O
day VB O
of NN O
training NN O
at DT O
Soarin' NNP O
in NN O
Epcot NNP B-ORG
http//tco/c9rtZyzEJh NN O

Romy NNP B-PER
keep NN O
talking VB O
bout NN O
Corey NNP B-PER
💀😭 NN O

@ijustdgad_22 NN B-PER
interesting NN O
loL NN O

@lordejosh JJ B-PER
Uncle NNP O
Drewis NNP O
the NN O
best NN O
point NN O
guard NN O
in NN O
the NN O
league NN O

@katiegonewild NN B-PER
@SleazyC_ JJ B-PER
wrong NN O
twitter NN B-ORG
name RB O
KT NNP O
😂 NN O

So NNP O
sick NN O
of NN O
constantly NNS O
having VB O
head NN O
aches DT O

Going NNP O
0 CD O
to NN O
5000 CD O
I PRP O
see NN O

@tristan__holt NN B-PER
@_LittleeeRed JJ B-PER
she NN O
was VB O
kidding NN O
right NN O

i NN O
still JJ O
aint DT O
sleepin NN O

@zeldasghost JJ B-PER
@destinaay_ JJ B-PER

I PRP O
can't VB O
really NN O
explain NN O
it NN O
I'm PRP O
so NN O
into NN O
you NN O
🎶🎶 NN O

@Amayraniloves24 VB B-PER
were NN O
going NN O
in NN O
the NN O
morning NN O

Korchek NNP B-PER
needs JJ O
to NN O
play NN O
more NN O

I PRP O
really NN O
lost NN O
my NN O
id NN O
😤 NN O

I'll PRP O
try NN O
that NN O
with NN O
my NN O
green NN O
laser NN O
pointer NN O
Apparently DT O
I PRP O
can VB O
light NN O
a DT O
match VB O
with NN O
it NN O
- : O
didn't NN O
know NN O
that NN O
#conversationswithcheritt # B-MISC
#norm # O

@AristeguiOnline VB O
@m_ebrard JJ O
La VB O
linea NN O
12 CD O
del NN O
metro NN O
debe NN O
ser NN O
reconstruida NN O
desde NN O
su NN O
baseo VB O
sea NN O
hacerla VB O
de NN O
nuevo JJ O
Jacobo NNP O
@JcbZabludovsky JJ O

@crash_in_adidas NN B-PER
lol NN O
2 CD O
weeks NN O
before NN O
your NN O
birthday NN O
yeah NN O

Checking NNP O
in NN O
@ NN O
The NNP B-ORG
Westin NNP I-ORG
Savannah VB I-ORG
Harbor NNP I-ORG
Golf NNP I-ORG
Resort NNP I-ORG
& CC I-ORG
Spa NNP I-ORG
in NN O
Savannah VB B-LOC
GA VB I-LOC
https//tco/OJ1nkNpoiH NN O

Aw DT O
ya NN O
can't VB O
hide NN O
redneck NN O
might NN O
as DT O
well NN O
be NN O
proud NN O

@FistFullOfHATE_ JJ B-PER
my NN O
mom NN O
was VB O
asking DT O
about DT O
my NN O
loud NN O
friend JJ O
that NN O
always DT O
wanted VB O
nuggets JJ O
from JJ O
mcdonalds NN B-ORG
& CC O
how NN O
you NN O
were NN O
😂😂 NN O

my NN O
moms NN O
reaction NN O
to NN O
some NN O
songs NN O
are DT O
honestly NN O
the NN O
FUNNIEST NNP O
things NN O
ever NN O

I PRP O
swear NN O
@AbbadabbaMarkus VB B-PER
has VB O
to NN O
have VB O
at DT O
least NN O
40 CD O
pictures NN O
of NN O
Bae IN O
on NN O
her NN O
phone NN O
by NN O
now JJ O

Trying NNP O
to NN O
calm VB O
down NN O
after DT O
work NN O
Possibly NNP O
made VB O
a DT O
minor NN O
clerical NNS O
error NN O
Not NNP O
a DT O
big NN O
deal NN O
but NN O
my NN O
co-worker NNS O
put NN O
me NN O
in NN O
panic VB O
mode NN O
#relax # O

@chassuz JJ B-PER
Yep NNP O
next JJ O
they'll NN O
ban VB O
short NN O
skirts JJ O

I PRP O
been NN O
wanting VB O
to NN O
fight NN O
so NN O
bad VB O

Never NNP O
have VB O
the NN O
ever NN O
supported NN O
me NN O
& CC O
my NN O
desitions NN O

BEAST NNP O
MODE NNP O
HAT NNP O
SOLD NNP O
OUT NNP O
ONLINE NNP O

@brinaa_baby NN B-PER
you're NN O
better NN O
than NN O
that NN O

Was WRB O
it NN O
worth NN O
it NN O

@KendaPerez JJ B-PER
two NN O
of NN O
my NN O
favorite VB O
people NN O
@MMAFanRandy JJ B-PER
D NN O

Currently NNP O
balling VB O
my NN O
eyes NN O
at DT O
right NN O
now JJ O
@GreysABC NN B-PER
why NN O
did NN O
yall VB O
have VB O
to NN O
do NN O
this NN O

Pretty NNP O
blue NN O
eyes NN O
with NN O
a DT O
hypnotizing NN O
smile JJ O

#NowPlaying # O
UFO NNP O
- : O
Vigiland NNP B-ORG

@YUNGS4M JJ B-PER
chill JJ O

@_allisoonn_ NN B-PER

Almost DT O
got NN O
arrested DT O
cuz NN O
the NN O
cop NNS O
saw VB O
me NN O
counting NNS O
the NN O
drawer NN O
at DT O
work NN O
and DT O
thought NN O
I PRP O
was VB O
robbing NN O
it NN O
With NNP O
all DT O
the NN O
lights NN O
on NN O
Like¿ NNP O
Ok NNP O

Waaaaay WRB O
up JJ O

@novaKAYne__ JJ B-PER
my NN O
baby NN O
turned NN O
20 CD O
today NN O
😳 NN O
he NN O
a DT O
old JJ O
man VB O
now JJ O
👴😂shut JJ O
up JJ O

😘 NN O

@trEAT_Me_GOOD_ NN B-PER
Goodnight NNP O
hope NN O
tomorrow NN O
is NN O
better NN O

FIZZZZZ NNP O
http//tco/xPwuZ6AQuh NN O

@jazdeee JJ B-PER
I'm PRP O
dying NN O

These NNP O
hoes NN O
clean NNS O
😩😩 NN O
RT@SneakerPics23 NNP O
Tianjin NNP B-LOC
Foams NNP O
releasing NN O
February NNP O
7th CD O
in NN O
China NNP B-LOC
http//tco/FsLkgCDSpC NN O

I PRP O
den NN O
put NN O
ALOT DT O
of NN O
niggas NN O
on NN O
& CC O
made VB O
ALOT DT O
of NN O
niggas NN O
FAMOUS😂😏😘 NNP O
u NN O
don't NN O
owe JJ O
me NN O
nothing JJ O
but NN O
I'm PRP O
yo NN O
DADDY NNP O
remember NN O
that NN O
BOY💯‼️💪 NNP O

@GamerCatHenri NN B-PER
Yeah NNP O
it's JJ O
hard NN O
to NN O
play NN O
online JJ O
too NN O
people NN O
lag NN O
when NN O
I PRP O
summon NN O
people NN O
into NN O
my NN O
world NN O
D NN O

@PhillyInquirer JJ B-ORG
McCord NNP B-PER
steps NN O
down NN O
amid DT O
signs NN O
of NN O
fed JJ O
probe NN O
http//tco/xqxyXcFZ3r NN O
Coincidence NNP O
you NN O
think NN O

@_chicho_6 JJ B-PER
thank NN O
you NN O

@MorgMilne JJ B-PER
I PRP O
love NN O
you NN O
Morg NNP B-PER
❤️❤️👯👊👌✌️ JJ O

@_kingking7 NN O
@calikid111 JJ O
happy VB O
g'day NN O
to NN O
the NN O
Yung NNP O
Gods NNP B-MISC

no NNS O
one JJ O
drive NN O
up JJ O
mt NN B-LOC
tabor VB I-LOC
road NN I-LOC

@Hannah_Orias NN B-PER
@marie_jolly6 JJ B-PER
Well NNP O
darn VB O
it NN O

#DayOff # O
#MotherSonDay # O
#5DollarFridayDeal # O
#Shopping # O
#StockingUpFor # O
#MyBoo❤️ # O
#Lunch # O
@ NN O
Safeway VB O
http//tco/Gojr4QX895 NN O

Someone NNP O
right NN O
now JJ O
come NNS O
up JJ O
to NN O
taco VB O
bell NN O
and DT O
please NN O
buy NN O
me NN O
a DT O
spicy JJ O
chicken JJ O
and DT O
or NN O
a DT O
crunch NNS O
wrap NN O
slider JJ O
or NN O
a DT O
griller NN O

@shelbymedic JJ B-PER
#dontbealonerthen # O

You NNP O
mad VB O
😏😂 NN O

Squad NNP O
http//tco/EFnf4p3koK NN O

I PRP O
hate VB O
when NN O
I PRP O
have VB O
an DT O
appnt DT O
for NN O
something NN O
and DT O
I PRP O
have VB O
to NN O
wait IN O
Annoyingggg DT O

Holeeeeeeeeeeee NNP O
shit NN O
snacks NN O
Over NNP O
500 CD O
notifications JJ O
I PRP O
don't NN O
even NN O
know NN O
where NN O
to NN O
start NN O
Most NNP O
have VB O
dropped NN O
off JJ O
I'm PRP O
sorry NN O
all DT O
TY NNP O
4 CD O
#FF<3 # O

Daves NNP B-PER
tryna NN O
tell NN O
me NN O
beginning NN O
of NN O
soph NN O
year NN O
he NN O
was VB O
the NN O
best NN O
at DT O
smash JJ O
@jonnywrangler JJ B-PER
@ry_deezy JJ B-PER
@Guy_Cerrito JJ B-PER

@KrablegzBScrong NN B-PER
@shelby_tfm JJ B-PER
but NN O
did NN O
he NN O
pee NN O
in NN O
ur JJ O
butt NN O
tho NN O
Nah NNP O
he NN O
got NN O
scared JJ O

Seriously NNP O
gotta NN O
start NN O
planning NN O
this NN O
trip NN O
heifers NN O
playing NN O
I PRP O
have VB O
no NNS O
problem NN O
going NN O
by NN O
myself NN O
just NN O
me NN O
and DT O
my NN O
bikini NN O
and DT O
my NN O
ID PRP O
😂😂😂 JJ O

Beyond NNP B-MISC
Scared NNP I-MISC
Straight NNP I-MISC
makes NN O
me NN O
so NN O
angry DT O
like NN O
how NN O
the NN O
hell NN O
you NN O
about DT O
to NN O
let NN O
your NN O
11 CD O
year NN O
old JJ O
get NN O
that NN O
out JJ O
of NN O
control NNS O

Anxiety DT O
really NN O
doesn't NN O
sit NN O
well NN O
with NN O
me NN O
😬😳 NN O

#missmeimonamission # O

Happy NNP O
birthday NN O
@brittt_boyerr NN B-PER
love NN O
youuu NN O
😘💗 NN O
http//tco/xQqDS3B9r0 NN O

I PRP O
still JJ O
ain't DT O
no NNS O
punk NN O
bitch NN O
but NN O
I PRP O
also DT O
learned NN O
that NN O
I PRP O
am DT O
so NN O
weak NN O
now JJ O
😭😭😭😭 JJ O
even NN O
more NN O
than NN O
before NN O

I PRP O
kinda NN O
enjoyed NN O
the NN O
campus VB O
today NN O
without NN O
all DT O
the NN O
extra NN O
people NN O
😂😂😂👌 JJ O

#MUSTREAD # O
@MasonNForbes JJ B-PER
Author DT O
of NN O
#Thriller # B-MISC
THE NNP O
STRONTIAN NNP O
FACTOR NNP O
UK NNP O
http//tco/av8o00EfxR NN O
US NNP O
http//tco/Zh7xrYV0b1 NN O
http//tco/n7E6gD91GJ NN O

@ithinkthatway NN B-PER
#DearFutureHusband # O
http//tco/iQlmTQADfxme NN O
as DT O
a DT O
wife NN O

@EDrenzek JJ B-PER
Had NNP O
a DT O
7 CD O
& CC O
7 CD O
just NN O
for NN O
you NN O
tonight NN O
Miss NNP O
you NN O

@maddietastor JJ B-PER
so NN O
sorry NN O
I PRP O
was VB O
sick NN O
and DT O
couldn't NNS O
make NN O
it NN O
I PRP O
hope NN O
you NN O
have VB O
an DT O
amazing DT O
night NN O
❤️❤️ JJ O

Baby NNP O
who NN O
are DT O
you NN O
trying NN O
to NN O
fool JJ O

@MccarthyColm JJ B-PER
good NN O
to NN O
know NN O

lmao NN O
Back IN O
in NN O
this NN O
bitch NN O
like NN O
I PRP O
parallel NN O
parking NN O

@brittt221 NN B-PER
I PRP O
don't NN O
even NN O
know NN O
tbh NN O

GM NNP O

@fabienneaj__ NN B-PER
Cosmo NNP O
& CC O
nursing RB O
are DT O
Both NNP O
a DT O
lot NN O
of NN O
book NN O
work NN O
so NN O
you NN O
prepare NN O
for NN O
that NN O
And DT O
you'll NN O
have VB O
to NN O
take VB O
an DT O
online JJ O
class NNS O
during NN O
summer NN O
😒🔫 NN O

@depecheomd JJ B-PER
@eReferenceDesk NN B-PER
@jlferguson50 JJ B-PER
@mohamad23325 JJ B-PER
@Yuta_Muto JJ B-PER
@Follow_Love39 JJ B-PER
@no1sumire JJ B-PER
@Nana_No77 NN B-PER
@F8O88 JJ B-PER
@top_member JJ B-PER
@ken_f12 JJ B-PER

@ShikkokuNoRenya JJ B-PER
Why NNP O
should NN O
I PRP O
get NN O
up JJ O

@JWKeady JJ B-PER
Like NNP O
2know CD O
why NN O
pols NN O
aren't DT O
forcing NN O
ins NN O
companies NNS O
2pay CD O
claims NNS O
2Sandy CD O
victims NN O
who NN O
had VB O
full JJ O
flood JJ O
cover-instead NNS O
have2 VB O
rebuild NN O
w NN O
grants NN O

Inside PRP O
a DT O
camera-slo VB O
mo NN O
guys NN O
http//tco/WZd7RYm6gY NN O

Funniest NNP O
movie NN O
I've PRP O
ever NN O
seen NN O

Guys NNP O
Please NNP O
help NN O
me NN O
out JJ O
Trying NNP O
to NN O
take VB O
my NN O
friends JJ O
cat VB O
to NN O
prom NN O
Please NNP O
rt NN O
@regisphiIbin JJ O
http//tco/zhHQv8gPNk NN O

It's PRP O
about DT O
to NN O
be NN O
a DT O
wild NN O
ride NN O

@BeyonceLand NN B-PER
Happy NNP O
Birthday NNP O
Justin NNP B-PER
Timberlake NNP I-PER
http//tco/0y9SXxGxPr NN O
❤️😻 JJ O

Can't VB O
wait IN O
to NN O
see NN O
my NN O
baby NN O
girl NN O
Bonnie NNP B-PER
today☺️😍 NN O

http//tco/WDv05RXwEY NN O

Watching WRB O
too NN O
cute NNS O
puts NN O
me NN O
in NN O
a DT O
good NN O
mood NN O
tbh NN O
🐶☺💚 JJ O

I PRP O
either NN O
lose NN O
sleep NN O
for NN O
you NN O
or NN O
because NN O
of NN O
you NN O

@alplicable VB O
you NN O
do NN O
it NN O
to NN O
yourself NN O
you NN O
do NN O
and DT O
that's NN O
what NN O
really NN O
hurts NN O
so NN O
true NN O

Babes NNP O
http//tco/XrOT38YRyI NN O

@MatteyTheDude JJ B-PER
I PRP O
should NN O
have VB O
put NN O
it NN O
in NN O
quotes NN O
I'm PRP O
not JJ O
going NN O
to NN O
love NN O
it NN O
when NN O
Lulu NNP B-MISC
and DT O
a DT O
Tesla NNP B-MISC
store NN O
is NN O
on NN O
the NN O
block NN O

So NNP O
much NN O
money NN O
on NN O
my NN O
mind NN O
thats NN O
all DT O
i NN O
remember NN O

@markhoppus JJ B-PER
she NN O
is NN O
betting NN O
it NN O
were NN O
someone NN O
different NN O
who NN O
knows NN O
she NN O
is NN O
always DT O
a DT O
hand VB O
away DT O

Tim NNP B-PER
Brown NNP I-PER
finally NN O
in NN O
the NN O
HOF NNP O
about DT O
time NN O

I PRP O
pissed NN O
on NN O
a DT O
pig NN O
& CC O
called VB O
it NN O
steak NN O

SONIC NNP B-ORG
Drive-In NNP O
Crew NNP O
Member NNP O
#Wichita # B-LOC
KS NNP I-LOC
http//tco/UBNhq62fox NN O
#Hospitality # O
#Job # O
#Jobs # O
#TweetMyJobs # O

Feel NNP O
like NN O
shait NN O
Ain't DT O
doing NN O
shit NN O
for NN O
the NN O
rest NN O
of NN O
the NN O
night NN O
now JJ O

@sar_uhhh6 NN B-PER
❤️❤️ JJ O

@gthomass7 JJ B-PER
h8rs NN O
+ NN O
thirst NN O
+ NN O
diet NN O
snapple NN O
= NN O
motivation NN O

#19inarow # O
is NN O
now JJ O
trending NN O
in NN O
#Atlanta # B-LOC
http//tco/DXdb9owzAI NN O

Midnight NNP O
sledding NN O
at DT O
East¿ VB O

@SportsCenter JJ B-ORG
#BoomerSooner # O

This NNP O
says VB O
it NN O
all DT O
LOL NNP O
http//tco/FWeIzGsn42 NN O

#callmesteven # O
I PRP O
lost NN O
all DT O
hope NN O
in NN O
ever NN O
getting NN O
a DT O
call VB O
from JJ O
u NN O

At DT O
Tri NNP B-ORG
City NNP I-ORG
Brewing NNP I-ORG
Company NNP I-ORG
pic NN O
— NN O
https//tco/g0Y43EjHg5 NN O

I PRP O
swear NN O
he NN O
told NN O
me NN O
that NN O
and DT O
it NN O
was VB O
actually DT O
pretty NN O
true NN O
until JJ O
I PRP O
met NN O
those NN O
nice NN O
people NN O
😊 NN O

Dancing NNP O
like NN O
@BandofNOTHING NN B-PER
is NN O
watching VB O

Whoever NNP O
is NN O
on NN O
YikYak NN B-ORG
saying VB O
shit NN O
about DT O
my NN O
sister NN O
being NN O
dramatic NN O
she NN O
just NN O
lost NN O
2 CD O
of NN O
her NN O
friends JJ O
to NN O
suicide JJ O
So NNP O
fuck JJ O
off JJ O
& CC O
grow NN O
up JJ O
#PavScum # O

Oh NNP O
puppy NN O
love… NN O
💕 NN O
http//tco/FV6ZVthSRE NN O

So NNP O
happy VB O
I PRP O
found JJ O
that NN O
portable NN O
charger NNS O
😂😍 NN O

When NNP O
you NN O
called VB O
me NN O
late NN O
last NN O
night NN O
were NN O
you NN O
faded VB O
Maybe NNP O
😏 NN O

This NNP O
nigga NN O
sick NN O
wo NN O
me NN O
Like NNP O
why NN O
text NN O
me NN O
2am CD O
talking VB O
shit NN O
& CC O
you NN O
NEVER NNP O
text NN O
Just NNP O
say VB O
you NN O
miss NN O
me NN O
pussy NN O
boy NN O
not JJ O
that NN O
I'll PRP O
gaf VB O
😂 NN O

@KKoncierge NN O
nah RB O
ik NN O
somebody NN O
who NN O
do NN O
tho NN O

Rick NN B-PER
Ross NNP I-PER
- : O
Burn NNP B-MISC
Hood NNP I-MISC
Billionaire NNP I-MISC
http//tco/utPVHgWTBg NN O

Kim NNP B-PER
so NN O
mean NN O
to NN O
me NN O
Fam NNP O

Dawg NNP O
Free NNP O
my NN O
fucking JJ O
brother NN O
http//tco/m85H3E0yG3 NN O

@jskylerinc JJ B-PER
True NNP O
- : O
it NN O
was VB O
very NN O
much NN O
written NN O
to NN O
create NNS O
as DT O
many VB O
gory NN O
deaths NN O
as DT O
possible NN O

@ForeignCedes JJ O
@xDeAsiaa_ JJ B-PER
#wakeuplikethis # O
#flawless # O

filling NN O
up JJ O
at DT O
$168 $ O
and DT O
only JJ O
paying VB O
$18 $ O
to NN O
fill NN O
my NN O
tank VB O
👍 NN O

@SportsGrid JJ B-MISC
Thats NNP O
a DT O
damn VB O
good NN O
idea//////I NN O
concur NNS O
completly NNS O
http//tco/rsMj1qDLwf NN O

@kimguilfoyle JJ B-PER
We'll NNP O
give NN O
the NN O
black NN O
hat VB O
to NN O
the NN O
babes NN O

@Pontifex JJ O
To NNP O
my NN O
knowledge NN O
facilitating VB O
the NN O
rapprochement VB O
between NN O
Cuba NNP B-LOC
and DT O
the NN O
USA NNP B-LOC
is NN O
your NN O
best NN O
accomplishment DT O
so NN O
farI VB O
we NN O
all DT O
Thank NNP O
You NNP O

@AsianFilmFestLA VB B-MISC
The NNP O
boys NN O
get NN O
serious NN O
about DT O
porn NN O
http//tco/Km7XFDokzl NN O
Please NNP O
visit/subscribe NN O
on NN O
RoHo NNP B-ORG
TV NNP I-ORG
for NN O
more NN O
#webseries # O
#fun # O

Barely IN O
the NN O
second NN O
class NNS O
meeting NN O
and DT O
already DT O
getting NN O
emails RB O
from JJ O
classmates NNS O
asking DT O
for NN O
the NN O
notes JJ O
😑 NN O

@rainbowedrose NN B-ORG
honestly NN O
if NN O
you're NN O
just NN O
going NN O
to NN O
switch JJ O
i NN O
wouldn't NN O
even NN O
bother NN O
making NN O
your NN O
character NNS O
on NN O
lamia NN O
i'd NN O
just NN O
wait IN O
for NN O
the NN O
server NN O

Everytime NNP O
I PRP O
try NN O
to NN O
get NN O
my NN O
life NN O
together NN O
something NN O
goes NN O
wrong NN O

@JohnsonsCherry JJ B-PER
oh NN O
no NNS O
please NN O
anything DT O
but NN O
that NN O
😂 NN O

I'm PRP O
at DT O
Plaza NNP B-LOC
La VB I-LOC
Rosa NNP I-LOC
in NN O
Mexico NNP B-LOC
City NNP I-LOC
Mexico NNP I-LOC
w/ NN O
@dagoed NN B-PER
@hilda_hdz JJ B-PER
https//tco/mrEKyc6RS4 NN O

Them NNP O
5lbs CD O
I PRP O
lost NN O
bout NN O
to NN O
be NN O
gained NN O
back VB O
by NN O
time NN O
I PRP O
go NN O
to NN O
my NN O
next JJ O
prenatal NN O
visit NN O

Forgive NNP O
to NN O
easily VB O

@WWEUniverse JJ B-ORG
@HEELZiggler NN B-PER

@PatDollard NN B-PER
@wendymadeve JJ B-PER
He NNP O
found JJ O
out JJ O
they NN O
speak NN O
English NNP O
at DT O
Oxford NNP B-LOC
wasn't VB O
sure NN O
if NN O
a DT O
translator NN O
was VB O
available DT O

I PRP O
want VB O
summer NN O

@AP VB O
@GOP JJ O
Why NNP O
Are DT O
You NNP O
Not NNP O
#RepealObamacare # O
What NNP O
did NN O
WE NNP O
elect NN O
You NNP O
For NNP O
RU NNP O
K NNP O
Street NNP O
#KockaRoaches # O
#DefundObamaPolicy # O
#ThePeoplesMandate # O

@stuffedschell7 JJ B-PER
http//tco/e6b0rp4oBq NN O

I PRP O
got NN O
punched NN O
stepped NN O
on NN O
with NN O
heels NN O
and DT O
pushed NN O
all DT O
over JJ O
the NN O
place NN O
like NN O
it NN O
was VB O
all DT O
bad VB O

Come NNP O
cuddle NNS O
me NN O
plz NN O

Guys NNP O
don't NN O
understand JJ O
the NN O
stomach NN O
pain IN O
we NN O
go NN O
through NN O
when NN O
they NN O
try NN O
beating NN O
it NN O
up JJ O

I PRP O
changed NNS O
for NN O
the NN O
better NN O
switched JJ O
up JJ O
now JJ O
im NN O
seeing NN O
brighter NN O
days VB O
#YGz # B-ORG
#Gang # O

Think NNP O
it NN O
ova NN O
Bitch NNP O
Im PRP O
thinkin NN O
forward NN O

🆙 NN O

Energy NNP O
giver NN O
award DT O
winner NN O
Congrats NNP O
http//tco/ymDu55jLqQ NN O

Star NNP O
former NN O
@cunyjschool JJ B-PER
student NN O
@pauldebenedetto NN B-PER
finds NN O
journalism NN O
in NN O
Texas NNP B-LOC
to NN O
be NN O
an DT O
embarrassment NN O
of NN O
riches NN O

Taste VB O
of NN O
LIttle NNP O
Italy PRP O
kicks NN O
off JJ O
at DT O
300 CD O
today NN O
We NNP O
will NN O
be NN O
there NN O
all DT O
weekend NN O
Stop NNP O
by NN O
and DT O
say VB O
hi NN O
#tasteoflittleitlay # O
http//tco/thnkQVninT NN O

@Chubbies JJ B-PER
Date NNP O
night NN O
http//tco/w39MPTBBwu NN O
@TheGreatJimboni JJ B-PER

I PRP O
have VB O
a DT O
thing NN O
for NN O
window NN O
displays NN O
Thanks NNP O
#FIDM # O
#ChristianLouboutin # B-PER
@ NN O
Cesar NNP B-ORG
Palace VB I-ORG
Las VB B-LOC
Vegas NNP I-LOC
Nevada NNP I-LOC
http//tco/szASGtvcCx NN O

Obama NNP B-PER
was VB O
for NN O
real NN O
born NN O
in NN O
Kenya NNP B-LOC
#UFF # O

I PRP O
can't VB O
see NN O
what NN O
I PRP O
can't VB O
relate NN O
to NN O

@nfl JJ B-ORG
@Seahawks JJ B-ORG
@RobGronkowski JJ B-PER
Sea NNP O
DB NNP O
wanted VB O
people NN O
to NN O
start NN O
talking VB O
football JJ O
again DT O
& CC O
not JJ O
about DT O
Brady's NNP O
BALLS IN O
- : O
Gronk NNP B-PER
has VB O
felt JJ O
them NN O
often JJ O

@teeny_gloyd JJ O
too NN O
fucking JJ O
true NN O

less NN O
than NN O
a DT O
month NN O
left NN O
https//tco/n3niQkjIoj NN O

@Micah_Doo JJ B-PER
I'll PRP O
text NN O
you NN O
rn NN O

RIP NN O
to NN O
everyone's NN O
friendship JJ O
😂😂 NN O

This NNP O
part NN O
of NN O
us JJ O
been NN O
gone NN O
for NN O
so NN O
long NN O

200medley CD O
relay-1st NN O
in NN O
district NN O

20👴 CD O
http//tco/Fm3cHnc2i0 NN O

South NNP B-LOC
Carolina VB I-LOC
swag NN O
lmfao NN O
http//tco/9tThNeFJQz NN O

#Accounting # O
#Job # O
alert DT O
Staff NNP O
Accountant DT O
| NN O
Robert NNP B-ORG
Half NNP I-ORG
Finance NNP I-ORG
& CC I-ORG
Accounting DT I-ORG
| NN O
#SanFranciscoorPaloAlto # B-LOC
CA VB I-LOC
http//tco/gyabHXYCP9 NN O

I PRP O
wanna VB O
see NN O
the NN O
boy NN O
next JJ O
door NN O

@VinJackson987 JJ B-PER
are DT O
u NN O
going NN O

@_TooShortSHA JJ B-PER
oop JJ O
😂💀 NN O

Can VB O
I PRP O
just NN O
hit NN O
1k CD O

Just NNP O
posted NN O
a DT O
photo NN O
@ NN O
Pat'e VB B-ORG
Palo VB I-ORG
European NNP I-ORG
Brasserie NNP I-ORG
http//tco/WZLMV4ylck NN O

@heyyhaleyg NN B-PER
haha VB O
Nooo NNP O
it NN O
was VB O
a DT O
letter NN O
I PRP O
sent NN O
that NN O
got NN O
sent NN O
back VB O
to NN O
me NN O
cause VB O
there NN O
was VB O
no NNS O
stamp NN O
😒 NN O

That NNP O
my NN O
friends JJ O
is NN O
FUCKING NNP O
GROSS NNP O
#fuckdat # O

OMFG NNP O
ARE DT O
YOU NNP O
SERIOUS NNP O

Stop NNP O
bragging NN O
on NN O
the NN O
little NN O
stuff NN O
Humble NNP O
that NN O
shit NN O
man VB O
Yeen NNP O
the NN O
only JJ O
one JJ O
doing NN O
it NN O

I'm PRP O
so NN O
sad VB O
that NN O
people NN O
in NN O
life NN O
live NN O
to NN O
make NN O
others JJ O
miserable NN O

@pwilly27 JJ B-PER
@hgragert NN B-PER
Exactly NNP O
what NN O
I PRP O
was VB O
thinking NN O

Goat NNP O
is NN O
a DT O
cool NNS O
kid NN O

@kamarisyrie NN B-PER
@LoveMorgan_ JJ B-PER
nope JJ O
she NN O
is NN O
staying NN O
up JJ O
to NN O
text NN O
me NN O
like NN O
we're NN O
not JJ O
in NN O
the NN O
same VB O
room NN O

Sav VB O
💀 NN O

You NNP O
ever NN O
had VB O
that NN O
scared JJ O
feeling JJ O
of NN O
losing NN O
the NN O
person NN O
you NN O
love NN O

Get NNP O
this NN O
work NN O
in NN O
with NN O
brother NN O
Mack NNP B-PER
real NN O
quick NN O

@stanbrown_745 JJ B-PER
Bro NNP O
Niggas NNP O
Already DT O
Kno NNP O
It PRP O
Ain't DT O
No NNP O
Competition NNP O
With NNP O
Us NNP O

@IVXVIIF96 NN B-PER
انا JJ O
موقود JJ O

😡 NN O

@CNBCPolitics JJ B-ORG
USA NNP B-ORG
failed VB O
to NN O
Hang NNP O
euro_Corporatism NN O
Leadership NNP O
who NN O
unleashed JJ O
Corpo_Fascism NNP O
1922-1945 CD O
USA NNP B-ORG
now JJ O
INFECTED PRP O
http//tco/gHUD9bpNtJ NN O

@tim_cook JJ B-PER
great NN O
mission NN O
Chinese NNP B-MISC
need JJ O
ability DT O
to NN O
expand NN O
their NN O
horizons NN O
WAREAGLE WRB O

TAKE VB O
A DT O
HIKE NNP O
BITCH NNP O
#makapuumornings # B-LOC
WE NNP O
DID NNP O
THIS NNP O
#lawbreakers # O
bowls123 NN O
@ NN O
Makapuu NNP B-LOC
Lighthouse NNP I-LOC
Trail NNP I-LOC
http//tco/B4q1xzufLK NN O

@DallasBlunt NN B-PER
@AHullYo VB B-PER
ewwww NN O
😷😷😷 JJ O

@Megan_Eliz606 JJ B-PER
were NN O
supposed NN O
to NN O
me NN O
moving NN O
to NN O
Florida NNP B-LOC
and DT O
that's NN O
the NN O
closest NNS O
gym NN O
to NN O
where NN O
i NN O
might NN O
me NN O
moving NN O

I PRP O
just NN O
got NN O
done NN O
testing NN O
😭😭😭😭 JJ O

@BasebaIIVines NN B-PER
When NNP O
you NN O
hit NN O
a DT O
bomb NN O
😂👍 NN O
https//tco/G9BN7udzSj NN O
😂😂 NN O

you'll NN O
cry NNS O
a DT O
river NN O
behind NN O
me NN O
then NN O

@chlo_fletch JJ B-PER
good NN O

how NN O
did NN O
I PRP O
lose NN O
my NN O
only JJ O
bra NN O

Happy NNP O
birthday NN O
Chaz NNP O
From NNP O
what NN O
I PRP O
can VB O
remember NN O
we NN O
had VB O
too NN O
much NN O
fun JJ O
lol NN O
#happybirthday # O
#drunk # O
#selfie… # O
http//tco/1x6kOHKYGd NN O

@TruthDrivenLife NN B-PER
ιғ NN O
a DT O
cнιcĸen NNS O
can VB O
нave VB O
lιpѕ NN O
❥༠ི༽ RB O
🐓 NN O
> NN O
🐔 NN O
' '' O
åıṅṭ JJ O
ṅọ NN O
ṡṭọƿƿıṅɢ JJ O
ȗṡ NN O
ི NN O
ི NN O
http//tco/UiPCkroqnU NN O

I'd PRP O
b NN O
more NN O
upset JJ O
if NN O
I PRP O
valued NN O
your NN O
opinion IN O

#OutlanderRewind # B-MISC
Love NNP O
the NN O
interaction NN O
with NN O
Rupert NNP B-PER
& CC O
Claire NNP B-PER
and DT O
now JJ O
we've NN O
seen NN O
the NN O
extended NN O
version NN O

@kirksmistress JJ B-PER
@kendal_la JJ B-PER
still JJ O
love NN O
this NN O
selfie NN O

Sectorrr NNP O
6😜 CD O

I PRP O
so NN O
did NN O
not JJ O
miss NN O
math VB O
homework NN O

@_TheyCallMeJae JJ B-PER
😂😂😂 JJ O
I PRP O
fwy JJ O

he's NN O
yelling NN O
at DT O
nothing JJ O
tbh NN O
http//tco/qJvfuqxODm NN O

I PRP O
believe NN O
that NN O
unarmed JJ O
truth NN O
and DT O
unconditional JJ O
love NN O
will NN O
have VB O
the NN O
final NN O
word NN O
in NN O
reality NN O
#MLKJr # O

@Irbise NN B-PER
dzięki NN O

8 CD O
AM DT O
ALERT DT O
Chicago's NNP O
electricity NN O
generation NN O
now JJ O
at DT O
its NN O
dirtiest NN O
http//tco/Uxr4J4WUgy NN O
#ChicagoGrowEfficiently # O

I PRP O
really NN O
should NN O
get NN O
started NN O
on NN O
my NN O
hair NN O
though NN O

I PRP O
miss NN O
Miami NNP B-LOC
😢🌅 NN O

I'm PRP O
thinking NN O
whataburger NN O

Don't NNP O
feel JJ O
like NN O
going NN O
to NN O
work NN O
later NN O

No NNP O
time NN O
for NN O
frowning JJ O
when NN O
it's JJ O
so NN O
beautiful NN O
out JJ O

Happy NNP O
MLK NNP B-MISC
Day NNP I-MISC

@victoriaa__6 JJ B-PER
go NN O
do NN O
that NN O
tho NN O

I PRP O
miss NN O
it NN O

@Entrepreneur JJ B-ORG
@AmitAvner VB B-PER
Drawing NNP O
attention DT O
for NN O
the NN O
moment NN O
to NN O
the NN O
ad DT O
is NN O
easy VB O
capturing VB O
that NN O
into NN O
actual DT O
sales VB O
that NN O
is NN O
the NN O
challenge NNS O

Fml NNP O
I PRP O
hate VB O
being NN O
sick NN O
b4 NN O
game VB O
days VB O

I PRP O
bite NN O
my NN O
tongue NN O
atleast DT O
20 CD O
times NN O
a DT O
day VB O
to NN O
prevent NN O
myself NN O
from JJ O
saying VB O
something NN O
really NN O
fucking JJ O
stupid NN O

tell NN O
me NN O
between NN O
@Seahawks JJ B-ORG
& CC O
@Patriots NN B-ORG
We NNP O
have VB O
both NN O
hats VB O
for NN O
sale VB O
at DT O
work NN O
which NN O
should NN O
I PRP O
get NN O
I PRP O
do NN O
like NN O
the NN O
Seattle NNP B-LOC
green NN O
#SEAvsPATS # O
#SB49 # O

Ass DT O
is NN O
juss NN O
great NN O

Had NNP O
a DT O
chill JJ O
day VB O
#blasian # O
@ NN O
grandma NN O
ficks NN O
house😂 NN O
http//tco/QU18gXIEn5 NN O

@DonnaFins JJ B-PER
@Stax1022 JJ B-PER
@HurtigN NN B-PER
I PRP O
just NN O
deleted NN O
that NN O
some NN O
how NN O
Have NNP O
baby NN O
in NN O
my NN O
arms DT O
lol NN O

@BroKeNFPS_ NN B-PER
is NN O
that NN O
your NN O
gt NN O

@itsdaniellef NN B-PER
😂😂😂 JJ O
don't NN O
we NN O
all DT O

@Mochahontass_ JJ B-PER
Amen DT O
@bombdarskinn NN B-PER
http//tco/YoUCrOWPG2 NN O
yes NN O
🙌 NN O

MSLSJSOAKSBAAP NNP O
@AndrewCassara VB B-PER
ILYYYSM PRP O
http//tco/KMm6BgiWqr NN O

I'd PRP O
rather VB O
be NN O
with NN O
someone NN O
that NN O
will NN O
tell NN O
me NN O
to NN O
stfu NN O
than NN O
someone NN O
that NN O
just NN O
agrees DT O
with NN O
everything NN O
I PRP O
say VB O

@loather JJ B-PER
@adr VB B-PER
Job NNP O
Requirements NNP O
uterus JJ O
boobs NN O

what NN O
even NN O
are DT O
we NN O
http//tco/YIcDNmTU6i NN O

Come NNP O
home NN O
to NN O
find NN O
some NN O
assholes DT O
tipped NN O
over JJ O
most NN O
of NN O
the NN O
garbage NN O
cans VB O
in NN O
our NN O
alley DT O

@xo_leahbrown_xo JJ B-PER
aka DT O
I PRP O
was VB O
in NN O
the NN O
house NN O
longer NN O
than NN O
you NN O

a DT O
'lil POS O
throwback NN O
w NN O
Mr NNP B-PER
Pluto🐶 NNP I-PER
@ NN O
Disneyland NNP B-ORG
http//tco/I11RwVEZSd NN O

Glizzy NNP O
Gang VB O

I PRP O
see NN O
- : O
Drinking NNP O
a DT O
Ten NNP B-MISC
Hills NNP I-MISC
Pale VB I-MISC
Ale DT I-MISC
by NN O
@GooseIsland JJ B-ORG
at DT O
@slaters5050 JJ B-LOC
— NN O
http//tco/5HLmR0AlFy NN O
#photo # O

@Cody JJ B-PER
mine NN O
is NN O
@skatemaloley NN B-PER

@BTuckerTorch NN O
@WNSource JJ O
We NNP O
Want WRB O
Stevie NNP B-PER
Ray VB I-PER
#TheBandIsBackTogether # O

You NNP O
have VB O
no NNS O
chill JJ O
bro NN O

Yes…@Rodeo5Mary NNP B-PER

Like NNP O
I PRP O
have VB O
friends JJ O
to NN O
talk VB O
to NN O
but NN O
I PRP O
want VB O
someone NN O
I PRP O
can VB O
go NN O
to NN O
a DT O
certain NNS O
level NN O
with NN O
and DT O
just NN O
have VB O
a DT O
deep NN O
conversation NNS O
Rare VB O
to NN O
find NN O

@Jaydb74 JJ B-PER
I'm PRP O
working NN O
on NN O
it NN O

@LaurGilll NN B-PER
CAN VB O
WE NNP O
JAM NNP O
TO NNP O
DIS NNP O
ASAP DT O

😋👑 NN O
I PRP O
love NN O
you NN O
and DT O
I'm PRP O
always DT O
here NN O
if NN O
you NN O
need JJ O
to NN O
talk VB O
or NN O
anything DT O
😘 NN O

I PRP O
could NNS O
litterally NN O
stay NN O
up JJ O
all DT O
night NN O
and DT O
literally NN O
do NN O
nothing JJ O
#insomnia # B-MISC
#needValium # B-MISC
#Percocet # B-MISC
#maybeXanax # B-MISC

Yo NNP O
Damien NNP B-PER
Lillard NNP I-PER
is NN O
not JJ O
from JJ O
this NN O
world NN O
lol NN O

I'm PRP O
getting NN O
sleepy NN O
😴 NN O

I'm PRP O
just NN O
trying NN O
to NN O
read NN O
your NN O
mind NN O

@arianayaffe VB B-PER
holy NN O
shit NN O
I PRP O
just NN O
tweeted NN O
an DT O
appreciation DT O
tweet NN O
lol NN O

you NN O
gotta NN O
crave NNS O
it NN O
enough NN O
2 CD O
taste VB O
it NN O

@PanthersD100 NN B-PER
@5TPershing RB B-PER
@IXLLearning NN B-ORG
84 CD O
hrs NN O
is NN O
quite NN O
impressive JJ O
#teamwork # O
#proudAP # O

I've PRP O
had VB O
my NN O
braces NN O
for NN O
a DT O
year NN O
and DT O
a DT O
half VB O
and DT O
honestly NN O
my NN O
teeth NN O
were NN O
straighter NN O
without NN O
them NN O
Like NNP O
what NN O
the NN O
fuck JJ O

im NN O
so NN O
tired NN O
😭 NN O
I PRP O
should've NN O
slept NN O
early VB O

Buying NNP O
our NN O
Vegas NNP B-LOC
flights JJ O
tonight NN O
TOO NNP O
EXCITED NNP O

@21inc RB B-ORG
Awesome DT O
paid IN O
#OceanPath # B-MISC
fellowships JJ O
for NN O
new JJ O
grads NN O
from JJ O
@stfxuniversity JJ B-ORG
@uOttawa JJ B-ORG
@McGillU JJ B-ORG
and DT O
@queensu JJ B-ORG
https//tco/FmmoCLuJLR NN O

Someone NNP O
text NN O
me NN O
😭 NN O

Heart NNP O
monitors NN O
r NN O
so NN O
comfy NNS O
Especially NNP O
when NN O
u NN O
sleep NN O
like NN O
yes NN O
It PRP O
feels JJ O
so NN O
good NN O
cutting NNS O
off JJ O
ur JJ O
circulation NN O
& CC O
not JJ O
an DT O
in NN O
convince NNS O
at DT O
all DT O

I PRP O
made VB O
it NN O
to NN O
season NN O
4 CD O
of NN O
AHS DT O
fam VB O

I'm PRP O
Thurl NNP B-PER
for NN O
them NN O
but NN O
with NN O
nun JJ O
to NN O
wear NN O
with NN O
it NN O

Thank NNP O
you NN O
@radboyukillem NN B-PER
for NN O
taking VB O
care VB O
of NN O
me NN O
and DT O
my NN O
cold NNS O
😷 NN O
http//tco/6RWKsEjJF0 NN O

@nafree_bella NN B-PER
question NN O
If PRP O
you NN O
hate VB O
America DT B-LOC
why NN O
are DT O
you NN O
here NN O

That NNP O
gym NN O
ses NN O
was VB O
on NN O
point NN O

@michelleswain33 JJ B-PER
@VcidVrin JJ B-PER
@kristiparsons12 NN B-PER
love NN O
you NN O
more NN O
babe😻 NN O

Randomly VB O
thinkingstill NN O
can't VB O
believe NN O
you're NN O
gone NN O
😔💔👼 JJ O
http//tco/3demEHH4VV NN O

can VB O
never JJ O
decide NN O
between NN O
the NN O
original IN O
and DT O
the NN O
acoustic DT O
version NN O

I'm PRP O
bouta NN O
go NN O
to NN O
bed😪 NN O

Cause VB O
this NN O
being NN O
mad VB O
Shit NNP O
getting NN O
boring NN O

When NNP O
I PRP O
get NN O
stressed NN O
I PRP O
watch VB O
documentaries NN O
on NN O
wild NN O
animals DT O
🐯🐗🐘 JJ O
that's NN O
not JJ O
weird NN O
right NN O

@WowBeerGifs JJ O
Hold NNP O
my NN O
beer NN O
while NN O
I PRP O
surf NN O
in NN O
the NN O
bathtub VB O
http//tco/42aLF4TbkT NN O
what NN O
did NN O
she NN O
think NN O
was VB O
gonna NN O
happen VB O

on NN O
a DT O
brighter NN O
note JJ O
i NN O
am DT O
30 CD O
weeks NN O
today NN O
10 CD O
weeks NN O
till NN O
my NN O
precious NN O
gets NN O
here NN O
👯 NN O
definitely NN O
gonna NN O
be NN O
a DT O
mommys NN O
girl NN O

@biancalovely NN O
@pureblisspromo JJ O
@pureblissmodels JJ O
@weeklypromo JJ O
@pbexposure NN O
@teampurebliss JJ O
@tweetproblaster JJ O
i NN O
appreciate DT O
the NN O
deal NN O
#Respect # O

Wat WRB O
is NN O
yur NN O
@ NN O
button NN O
broken NN O

this NN O
that NN O
knock NN O
😂🎧 NN O
http//tco/ONqtrWGUds NN O

What NNP O
ever NN O
happened VB O
to NN O
the NN O
black NN O
eyed NN O
peas NN O
I PRP O
used JJ O
to NN O
love NN O
them😂 NN O

Tomorrow NNP O
is NN O
jogging NN O
pants VB O
and DT O
long NN O
sleeve NN O
weather NN O
but NN O
I PRP O
don't NN O
have VB O
jogging NN O
pants VB O
😪😭💔 JJ O

@Redheadedhoney_ JJ B-PER
I PRP O
made VB O
it NN O
up JJ O
specifically NN O
for NN O
you NN O

@AG_rocks VB O
SS NNP O
BOYZ NNP O
COZY NNP O
NEVER NNP O
RELAX NNP O
No NNP O
time NN O
to NN O
relax NN O

Congrats NNP O
2 CD O
Rafa VB B-PER
Nadal NNP I-PER
4 CD O
ur JJ O
nail IN O
biting NN O
win NN O
over JJ O
Smyczek NNP B-PER
6-2 CD O
3-6 LS O
6-7 CD O
6-3 CD O
7-5 CD O
Give NNP O
a DT O
girl NN O
a DT O
heart NN O
attack DT O
why NN O
don'tcha NN O
Rafa/Zankie VB B-PER
killin NN O
me NN O

Today NNP O
I PRP O
thought NN O
about DT O
you NN O
I PRP O
thought NN O
Erykah NNP B-PER
remember NN O
when NN O
he NN O
And DT O
before NN O
I PRP O
could NNS O
get NN O
all DT O
😍 NN O
I PRP O
remembered NN O
when NN O
he NN O
had VB O
me NN O
fucked JJ O
up JJ O
🙅 NN O

I PRP O
love NN O
Calum VB B-PER

@lm_MysT JJ B-PER
Message NNP O
Gt NNP B-MISC
and DT O
I'll PRP O
get NN O
back VB O
to NN O
ya NN O

Got NNP O
my NN O
glasses NN O
today😍😍😍 NN O

Criminal NNP B-MISC
minds NN I-MISC
is NN O
by NN O
far VB O
the NN O
best NN O
tv NN O
show NN O
😳 NN O

@mkisch44 JJ B-PER
🙈🙈🙈 JJ O
I PRP O
DONT NNP O
KNOW NNP O

Special NNP O
treat NN O
at DT O
NW NNP B-ORG
Film NNP I-ORG
Center NNP I-ORG
tonight NN I-ORG
-- : O
program NN O
for NN O
Portland NNP B-ORG
International PRP I-ORG
Film NNP I-ORG
Festival NNP I-ORG
Get NNP O
ready… NN O
http//tco/dcJq97yHk2 NN O

I PRP O
feel JJ O
like NN O
I'm PRP O
the NN O
only JJ O
one JJ O
that NN O
has VB O
never JJ O
been NN O
to NN O
BWW NNP B-LOC

#MissUniverse2014 # O
# # O
Miss NNP O
Myanmar NNP B-LOC
@MsUniverseCrown JJ O
http//tco/EDQLYbyEod NN O

Just NNP O
passed VB O
test NN O
number JJ O
2 CD O
Now NNP O
I PRP O
can VB O
relax NN O
and DT O
prepare NN O
for NN O
test NN O
number JJ O
3 CD O

Warriors WRB B-ORG
too NN O
nice NN O

Never NNP O
appreciated DT O
music NN O
that NN O
promoted NN O
wrong NN O
doing NN O
in NN O
a DT O
relationship NN O
That NNP O
shiz NN O
just NN O
gets NN O
me NN O

Me NNP O
54 CD O
mom NN O
84 CD O
my NN O
biggest NN O
fan VB O
my NN O
mom NN O
loves NN O
her NN O
to NN O
life NN O
@ NN O
Church NNP B-LOC
Ave DT I-LOC
Brooklyn NNP I-LOC
http//tco/RJ4W7gv0UD NN O

I PRP O
don't NN O
have VB O
to NN O
change NNS O
your NN O
mind NN O
I PRP O
just NN O
wanna VB O
take VB O
your NN O
time🎶 NN O
#samhunt # O

S/O NNP O
http//tco/WQhIEdPfXL NN O

school JJ O
is NN O
ruining NN O
my NN O
social NN O
life NN O

Me NNP O
& CC O
Lex NNP B-PER
bored NN O

Work NNP O
& CC O
twerk NN O
that NN O
body NN O

Tonight NNP O
on NN O
Coast NNP B-ORG
to NN I-ORG
Coast NNP I-ORG
7-9 CD I-ORG
Yitta NN B-PER
Halberstam NNP I-PER
discusses NN O
visiting NN O
deceased NN O
relatives NN O
and DT O
loved NN O
ones JJ O
in NN O
their NN O
dreams NN O
http//tco/lrQPp9guPM NN O

Chipotle NNP B-ORG

^^^ JJ O

Like NNP O
I PRP O
don't NN O
wanna VB O
talk VB O
to NN O
another DT O
crazy/selfish/narcissistic/ NNS O
delusional/ NN O
weed NN O
chaser NNS O
dude NN O

Gotta NNP O
show NN O
some NN O
love NN O
to NN O
our NN O
stomping NN O
grounds NN O
#miami # B-LOC
#miamiartwalk # O
#artwalk # O
#streetart # O
#heart… # O
http//tco/1E4Lz1V1jG NN O

* NN O
العَالمُ JJ O
كَبيرٌ JJ O
جِداً JJ O
، NN O
و NN O
النَّاسُ JJ O
حَوْلي JJ O
كَثِيرُونَ JJ O
لَكِنِّي JJ O
مازلتُ JJ O
اشْعُرُ JJ O
انّني JJ O
وَحِيد JJ O

I PRP O
need JJ O
a DT O
car😩 VB O

@TheTrippyGod JJ B-ORG
positive NN O
minded NN O
http//tco/cqbIt4SnB3 NN O

Sometimes NNP O
the NN O
only JJ O
person NN O
you NN O
can VB O
trust NN O
is NN O
yourself💯💯💯 NN O

gonna NN O
watch VB O
the NN O
originals IN O
so NN O
no NNS O
one JJ O
bother NN O
me NN O
k NN O
k NN O
😊 NN O

I PRP O
need JJ O
to NN O
find NN O
my NN O
chill JJ O
before NN O
I PRP O
explode NN O

will NN O
someone NN O
plz NN O
love NN O
me NN O
as DT O
much NN O
as DT O
i NN O
love NN O
my NN O
aviii DT O

A DT O
judge NN O
said VB O
South NNP B-LOC
Dakota's NNP I-LOC
same VB O
sex NN O
marriage NN O
ban VB O
was VB O
wrong NN O
but NN O
I PRP O
ain't DT O
changing NNS O
it NN O
I PRP O
said VB O
the NN O
same VB O
thing NN O
when NN O
my NN O
ex NN O
caught VB O
me NN O
cheating NNS O

finna NN O
be NN O
a DT O
low NN O
life NN O
like NN O
you NN O
niggas NN O
that NN O
be NN O
on NN O
twitter NN O
all DT O
day VB O
😒 NN O
opposite JJ O
of NN O
goals NN O
af DT O

Mr NNP B-PER
Deeds NNP I-PER
is NN O
such NN O
a DT O
classic NNS O

Prolly NNP B-PER
go NN O
to NN O
the NN O
waters VB O
Saturday VB O
maybe VB O

@HJBillick NN B-PER
he NN O
has VB O
and DT O
it's JJ O
exploding NN O
everywhere NN O

Got NNP O
a DT O
new JJ O
guilty NN O
pleasure NN O
Anybody DT O
watching VB O
#BransonFamous # B-MISC
When NNP O
they NN O
break NN O
into NN O
song NN O
during NN O
the NN O
interludes NN O
is NN O
the NN O
best NN O
#CountryDrama # O

@Juergles JJ B-PER
#FiveWordsToRuinAFriendship # O
Please NNP O
sign NN O
my NN O
band VB O
tho NN O

@beebadonka NN B-PER
@Ayoo_Cesarrr VB B-PER
Long NNP O
hair NN O
don't NN O
care VB O
💁my JJ O
hair NN O
gets NN O
super NN O
curly NNS O
😂 NN O

@AJPunkIsMyWorld VB B-PER
Hogan's NNP O
the NN O
perfect NN O
guy NN O
for NN O
Macho NNP B-PER
Their NNP O
history NN O

@xxxlawley JJ B-PER
v NN O
awkward DT O

@jadieinthecity JJ B-PER
this NN O
should NN O
do NN O
it NN O
http//tco/tStpCOXTCs NN O

12 CD O
always DT O
see NN O
you NN O
around DT O
😁 NN O

And DT O
she NN O
thinks NN O
she'll NN O
be NN O
getting NN O
a DT O
ride NN O
in NN O
the NN O
beautiful NN O
black NN O
ranger VB O
😂😁 NN O
@Gage_Tyrrell99 NN B-PER

I PRP O
know NN O
Pitino NNP B-PER
wants VB O
to NN O
run NN O
and DT O
play NN O
up JJ O
tempo NN O
but NN O
I PRP O
don't NN O
think NN O
this NN O
team NN O
can VB O
handle VB O
it NN O

Aww DT O
fiona NN B-PER
you NN O
little NN O
angel DT O
mouse NN O
#aboutaboy # O

@katiedoe7 NN B-PER
im NN O
going NN O
to NN O
block NN O
u NN O
kt NN O

@sighmike JJ B-PER
Y NN O
ARE DT O
U NN O
LOOKING NNP O
DOWN NNP O
ALL DT O
THE NNP O
WRONG NNP O
ROADS NNP O

Sum NNP O
of NN O
yall VB O
just NN O
mad VB O
for NN O
no NNS O
reason NN O
😂 NN O

@LeslieCRoberts JJ B-PER
2015 CD O
resolution NN O
if NN O
it NN O
can't VB O
be NN O
served NN O
on NN O
a DT O
stick JJ O
I'm PRP O
not JJ O
gonna NN O
eat VB O
it NN O

rid NN O
me NN O
of NN O
myself NN O
I PRP O
belong NN O
to NN O
you🎶❤️🙌 NN O

Earliest NN O
I've PRP O
been NN O
in NN O
bed NN O
in NN O
weeks NN O

Feels NNP O
later NN O
then NN O
it NN O
actually DT O
is NN O

http//tco/iHNvY6lFRQ NN O

@IamMikeRich NN B-PER
no NNS O
luh NN O
lives NN O
herego NN O
to NN O
sleep NN O

Can't VB O
wait IN O
to NN O
move NN O
out JJ O
of NN O
CaliforniaI've VB O
lived NN O
here NN O
for NN O
18 CD O
years NN O
and DT O
I've PRP O
been NN O
all DT O
over JJ O
the NN O
state NN O

@garablegm NN B-PER
Whats NNP O
good NN O
I PRP O
can VB O
tell NN O
you NN O
would NN O
like NN O
this NN O
rap VB O
artist DT O
he NN O
is NN O
flame NN O
Listen NNP O
& CC O
download NN O
http//tco/YO7okW7Sm0 NN O
#ya # O
* NN O

Be NNP O
the NN O
labor NN O
great NN O
or NN O
smalldo JJ O
it NN O
well NN O
or NN O
not JJ O
at DT O
all DT O
The NNP O
result NN O
of NN O
not JJ O
being NN O
done NN O
right NN O
the NN O
1st… CD O
http//tco/m1s9WOg6p2 NN O

FAV NNP O
if NN O
active DT O

@NotAllBhas JJ O
OMFG NNP O
YOUR NNP O
BACK IN O
PRAISE NNP O
JESUS NNP O

#OakLawn # B-LOC
IL PRP I-LOC
#Retail # O
#Job # O
Health NNP O
Enthusiast NNP O
Part-Time VB O
at DT O
The NNP B-ORG
Vitamin NNP I-ORG
Shoppe NNP I-ORG
http//tco/28yOKPVeIq NN O
#Jobs # O
#TweetMyJobs # O

@AdrianaPaolaDel VB B-PER
@keyshlliam JJ B-PER
@Lil__Za JJ B-PER
@NilmarieAcosta JJ B-PER
tengo NN O
un JJ O
montón NN O
en NN O
cel NNS O
de NN O
nosotras JJ O
😔😭😰 JJ O

dogs NN O
are DT O
so NN O
annoying DT O
when NN O
it NN O
comes NNS O
to NN O
food JJ O

I PRP O
swear NN O
there's NN O
something NN O
in NN O
the NN O
water VB O
in NN O
newport JJ O
staying NN O
away DT O
from JJ O
that NN O
shit NN O
🙅🚫👶🚫 JJ O

Finally NNP O
done NN O
cleaning NNS O
my NN O
room NN O
I PRP O
need JJ O
a DT O
bigger NN O
closet NNS O
😒 NN O

LET NNP O
GO NNP O
LET NNP O
GOD NNP O

I PRP O
could NNS O
get NN O
it NN O
now JJ O
but NN O
my NN O
dad VB O
wants VB O
me NN O
to NN O
think NN O
about DT O
it😔 NN O

@kristaparry NN B-PER
I PRP O
was VB O
16 CD O
years NN O
old JJ O
My NNP O
PE NNP O
teacher NN O
introduced NN O
us JJ O
at DT O
a DT O
small JJ O
area DT O
called VB O
Oregon NNP B-LOC
Ridge NN I-LOC
near RB O
Balto IN B-LOC
MD NNP I-LOC
Not NNP O
there NN O
now JJ O

Wonderful NNP O
dinner NN O
date VB O
at DT O
Café VB B-ORG
Luna NNP I-ORG
with NN O
Leah❤️ NNP O
@ NN O
Caffe VB B-ORG
Luna NNP I-ORG
http//tco/6sdCaGDynV NN O

@Marofis JJ B-PER
We're NNP O
passionate VB O
about DT O
things NN O
we NN O
can't VB O
imagine NN O
NOT NNP O
doing NN O
for NN O
the NN O
rest NN O
of NN O
our NN O
lives NN O

@MeganDagenais JJ B-PER
@Chloe_Caswell05 JJ B-PER
lol NN O
that's NN O
my NN O
story NN O
rite NN O
now JJ O

bout NN O
to NN O
cry NNS O
to NN O
sleep NN O
wtf NN O
😢😢😢😢 JJ O

DRose NNP B-PER
how NN O
about DT O
playing NN O
a DT O
little NN O
D NN O

Scott NNP B-PER
Drew NNP I-PER
is NN O
trying NN O
to NN O
do NN O
Scott NNP B-PER
Drew NNP I-PER
things NN O
on NN O
ESPNU NNP B-ORG
right NN O
now JJ O

@jdhk_FreeSoul JJ B-PER
/ NN O
http//tco/on3f3k0ujpprops NN O

@_MrIncredible5 JJ B-PER
because NN O
of NN O
your NN O
facial VB O
hair NN O
haha VB O

I PRP O
don't NN O
want VB O
to NN O
deal NN O
with NN O
bangtan VB O
rn NN O
so NN O
I'm PRP O
going NN O
to NN O
go NN O
to NN O
sleep NN O

2 CD O
RIGHT NN O
LANES VB O
BLOCKED NNP O
at DT O
I-69 PRP B-LOC
SB/ NNP I-LOC
106th CD I-LOC
Street NNP I-LOC
Vehicle NNP O
flipped JJ O
over JJ O
Major NNP O
delays NN O
for NN O
other JJ O
drivers NN O
@rtv6 JJ B-ORG
@MarcMullins1 JJ B-PER
#traffic # O

Sub NNP O
For NNP O
Lacroix VB B-MISC
👌 NN O

So NNP O
when NN O
does NN O
this NN O
beauty NN O
regiment NN O
kick NN O
in NN O
#tiredashell # B-PER
and DT O
I PRP O
look NN O
like NN O
it NN O
too NN O

I PRP O
have VB O
absolutely DT O
no NNS O
idea NN O
on NN O
earth VB O
why NN O
Little NNP B-MISC
WomanLA NNP I-MISC
has VB O
captured VB O
my NN O
fascination VB O
@LittleWomanLA JJ B-MISC
I PRP O
can't VB O
stop NN O
http//tco/KGvBxWXGeB NN O

Supplemental NNP O
Health NNP O
Care VB O
RN NNP O
/ NN O
Registered NNP O
Nurse NNP O
/ NN O
Travel NNP O
#Boise # B-LOC
ID PRP I-LOC
http//tco/9oE1mWQxpG NN O
#Nursing # O
#Job # O
#Jobs # O
#TweetMyJobs # O

😂😂😂 JJ O
my NN O
friends JJ O
are DT O
EVIL NNP O

😂 NN O
same VB O
here NN O
bruh NN O
http//tco/0bbbiM6uUq NN O

@NattyBohs NN B-PER
hersh's NN O
pizza NN O
on NN O
light NN O
street NN O

Mail NNP O
order JJ O
brides NN O
> NN O
actual DT O
women NN O
with NN O
feelings JJ O

Our NNP O
orientation IN O
classes NNS O
have VB O
been NN O
rockin' NN O
their NN O
training NN O
AND DT O
these NN O
hairnets NN O
#FCEintern # O
http//tco/TpZS2F0Wa4 NN O

if NN O
u NN O
post NN O
about DT O
UR NNP O
party NN O
on NN O
Twitter NNP B-ORG
then NN O
you NN O
deserve NN O
everything NN O
comin NNS O
your NN O
way VB O
don't NN O
complain NNS O
😂 NN O

i NN O
like NN O
good NN O
food JJ O
& CC O
good NN O
company NNS O
to NN O
eat VB O
it NN O
with NN O

Lool NNP O
always DT O
whining NN O
😒 NN O

@teamrobhogg JJ B-PER
god NN O
I PRP O
remember NN O
those NN O
days VB O
When NNP O
did NN O
that NN O
stop NN O

@yungsavagetc JJ B-PER
@jaaaycash JJ B-PER
😂 NN O
chill JJ O
out JJ O
bruh NN O
fr NN O
fr NN O

Drinking NNP O
a DT O
Rebel NNP B-MISC
IPA PRP I-MISC
by NN O
@SamuelAdamsBeer NN B-ORG
@ NN O
Irish PRP B-ORG
Mill NNP I-ORG
— NN O
http//tco/55RBAFKEEB NN O

Okay NNP O
I'm PRP O
addicted DT O
to NN O
flow JJ O
free JJ O

Nikki NNP O
😍😍 NN O
http//tco/qMZLyHdA2m NN O

Who NNP O
is NN O
Bubba NNP B-PER

I PRP O
love NN O
me NN O
some NN O
him NN O
even NN O
without NN O
the NN O
funds JJ O

I PRP O
miss NN O
baseball VB O
so NN O
much NN O
I PRP O
can't VB O
wait IN O
to NN O
watch VB O
@MattFabela JJ B-PER
do NN O
work NN O
this NN O
year NN O

Crab NNP B-LOC
Orchar NNP I-LOC
Ky NNP I-LOC
Temp NNP O
is NN O
313°C CD O
Wind00mph NNP O
Pressure NNP O
3006hpa CD O
Rising NN O
slowly NN O
Rain VB O
Today NNP O
001mm CD O
Forecast NNP O
Fine NNP O
weather NN O

@SexualGif JJ O
What NNP O
do NN O
you NN O
see NN O
in NN O
that NN O
guy NN O
He NNP O
makes NN O
me NN O
laugh NN O
💋🐰 NN O
http//tco/f2UfzCHCPq NN O

@Johnny_Logic JJ B-PER
asssssholllllllllllle DT O

@spleen_31 JJ B-PER
not JJ O
in NN O
my NN O
eyes NN O
lol NN O

@mulattomontana JJ B-PER
@wrightpeighton NN B-PER
😂😂😂😂😂girly JJ O
can VB O
see NN O
after DT O
doe👀 NN O

@griffinkopec16 NN B-PER
@Pornhub JJ B-ORG
@coon_travis JJ B-PER
idk NN O
how NN O
I PRP O
even NN O
found JJ O
this NN O
its NN O
amazing😂😂😂😂 DT O
I PRP O
died NN O
when NN O
I PRP O
saw VB O
it NN O

@DetroitRedWings JJ B-ORG
@Allstate VB B-ORG
MrazekExcellent NNP O
play NN O
from JJ O
the NN O
young NN O
fella JJ O
He NNP O
had VB O
to NN O
be NN O
pumped NN O
watching VB O
Pav VB O

@_iAMthee JJ B-PER
@say_shelbss NN B-PER
@O_oDabney_DidIt JJ B-PER
Sharing NNP O

Take VB O
that NN O
shit NN O
back VB O
that's NN O
trappin NN O
interference NN O

@BestGreatHeroic NN B-PER
@mjthorpe96 JJ B-PER
I'm PRP O
not JJ O
saying VB O
Chuck NNP B-PER
wasn't VB O
still JJ O
good NN O
of NN O
course NNS O
he NN O
was VB O
just NN O
not JJ O
a DT O
top NN O
player NN O
in NN O
the NN O
league NN O
anymore DT O

@TwerkingVine JJ B-PER
Quote NNP O
this NN O
with NN O
a DT O
great NN O
hip NN O
to NN O
waist IN O
ratio VB O
pic NN O
We'll NNP O
RT NNP O
the NN O
best NN O
ones JJ O
http//tco/sQhAYDVohD NN O

@GoodmanESPN JJ B-ORG
@BReinkemeyer NN B-PER
@sportsjunkie94 JJ B-PER
^^^ JJ O

@tstroud1554 JJ B-PER
na IN O
man VB O
I'm PRP O
out JJ O
working NN O
http//tco/luhOZN60jd NN O

Happy NNP O
Birthday NNP O
Mrs NNP B-PER
Holmes NNP I-PER
Thanks NNP O
for NN O
all DT O
of NN O
your NN O
support NN O
for NN O
our NN O
team NN O
and DT O
for NN O
feeding JJ O
the NN O
Maryland NNP B-LOC
wrestling NN O
community NNS O
for NN O
so NN O
many VB O
years NN O

@Gabriel3Shalda NN B-PER
well NN O
shit NN O
Think NNP O
of NN O
one JJ O
😂😂😂 JJ O

Stayed NNP O
up JJ O
late NN O
for NN O
no NNS O
reason NN O
now JJ O
I'm PRP O
so NN O
tired NN O
😭 NN O

That's NNP O
all DT O
me NN O
😌😁 NN O

Kiss NNP O
my NN O
ass DT O

@southernbreanna JJ B-PER
its NN O
gross NN O

@_cheybby JJ B-PER
no NNS O
they NN O
rescheduled NN O
it NN O

@spiritualkilla_ JJ O
is NN O
the NN O
most NN O
hottest NN O
person NN O
ever😍😩🙈 NN O

Him NNP O
Your NNP O
Ugly NNP O
Me NNP O
Okay NNP O
and DT O
was VB O
that NN O
suppose NN O
to NN O
hurt NN O
my NN O
feelings JJ O
💁 NN O

@maize_rage JJ B-PER
if NN O
I PRP O
get NN O
a DT O
chance NNS O
to NN O
look NN O
again DT O
when NN O
I PRP O
walk VB O
back VB O
to NN O
Downtown NNP B-LOC
Disney NNP I-LOC
maybe VB O
later NN O
tonight NN O
I'll PRP O
look NN O
again DT O
😊 NN O

@SEBTSB JJ B-PER
PLEASE NNP O
FOLLOW NNP O
ME NNP O
😭🙏 NN O
http//tco/R5Ud4qimIB NN O

😂 NN O

Crime NNP O
shows NN O
piss NN O
me NN O
off JJ O
Who NNP O
goes NN O
to NN O
weird NN O
places NN O
to NN O
make NN O
out JJ O
Chill NNP O

I'm PRP O
not JJ O
chillin JJ O
with NN O
someone NN O
else NN O
tf NN O
I PRP O
look NN O
like NN O

@RudeAlexx JJ B-PER
@Psicotweetco JJ O
@xDeigelx JJ O
sia NN O
todo NN O

@carlcorcolon JJ B-PER
happy VB O
birthday NN O
Take VB O
care😄👍🎉 VB O

You NNP O
good NN O
dude NN O
@Chris_Rileyy JJ B-PER

#B4DAMONEY # B-MISC
4 CD O
days VB O
🙌 NN O
until JJ O
I'm PRP O
sane VB O
again DT O

Will NNP O
the NN O
exhaustion NN O
ever NN O
go NN O
away DT O
Recovering NNP O
from JJ O
foot JJ O
surgery NN O
is NN O
kicking NN O
my NN O
butt NN O
My NNP O
whole NN O
body NN O
hurts NN O
I've PRP O
hit NN O
a DT O
wall VB O
for NN O
sure NN O

@NaughtyBoyMusic NN B-PER
louis NN O
Has NNP O
a DT O
big NN O
dick NN O

@tristan_martino NN B-PER
Stfu NNP O
leafs NN O
suck+you NN O

When NNP O
bae VB O
isn't NN O
texting NN O
you NN O
http//tco/66gSuTw8lN NN O

I PRP O
be NN O
in NN O
my NN O
feelings JJ O
sometimes😩 NN O
but NN O
it NN O
never JJ O
last NN O
long😀 NN O
Shit NNP O
just NN O
don't NN O
get NN O
to NN O
me NN O
the NN O
way VB O
it NN O
used JJ O
to😐 NN O

@couchvodkas JJ B-PER
@KyleDoesKC JJ B-PER
Time NNP O
for NN O
sobriety NN O

get NN O
out JJ O
of NN O
my NN O
bed NN O
you NN O
lazy NN O
sack VB O
of NN O
shit NN O
- : O
me NN O
to NN O
shane NN B-PER
just NN O
now JJ O

Gorgeous NNP O
sunrise NN O
as DT O
I PRP O
leave NN O
the NN O
bay VB O
😊 NN O
http//tco/3HdV8RD3Js NN O

@AtEaseFilm VB B-PER
Good NNP O
luck NN O
with NN O
your NN O
indie NN O
premise NN O
is NN O
good NN O

@hill2laettner JJ B-PER
@BlueDevilLair NN B-PER
@ChrisBunn21 JJ B-PER
I PRP O
cant VB O
even NN O
watch VB O
the NN O
game VB O
today NN O
unfortunately JJ O

these NN O
hoes NN O
wishy NN O
washy VB O
aine DT O
no NNS O
doubt NN O
abt DT O
it NN O
👐 NN O

Big NNP O
shout NN O
out JJ O
to NN O
young NN O
buck NN O
Dunaway NNP O
for NN O
finding NN O
me NN O
a DT O
dog NN O

Some NNP O
in NN O
some NN O
out JJ O
#MakingMoves # O
@ NN O
Bank IN B-ORG
of NN I-ORG
America DT I-ORG
in NN O
Eugene NNP B-LOC
OR NNP I-LOC
https//tco/FMmQITzc9y NN O

Going NNP O
to NN O
sleep NN O
day VB O
messed NN O
up JJ O

@ChachiBobinks JJ B-PER
I PRP O
have VB O
a DT O
pair IN O
of NN O
scissors JJ O
Also DT O
no NNS O
cleanup NNS O
We NNP O
can VB O
cut NNS O
it NN O
on NN O
my NN O
front JJ O
porch NN O
and DT O
let NN O
the NN O
wind NN O
blow NN O
away DT O
the NN O
excess NN O

Its PRP O
cost NNS O
you NN O
nuthin JJ O
pay VB O
me NN O
no NNS O
mind NN O

Hmm NNP O
detox NN B-MISC
Island PRP I-MISC
smoothie JJ O
and DT O
a DT O
half VB O
sandwich VB O
sounds NN O
well NN O

Really NNP O
wish NN O
I PRP O
would've NN O
took NN O
high NN O
school JJ O
seriously NN O
😔 NN O

I PRP O
thought NN O
my NN O
birthday NN O
was VB O
next JJ O
week NN O
but NN O
it's JJ O
not JJ O
I'm PRP O
still JJ O
on NN O
drugs NN O

gotta NN O
stay NN O
high NN O

I PRP O
hate VB O
apple DT O
and DT O
their NN O
stupid NN O
ass DT O
security NN O
questions NN O
that NN O
it NN O
won't NN O
let NN O
me NN O
reset NN O
😡😡😡😡😡😡 JJ O

@lewis_ranch JJ B-PER
@LoverMathias JJ B-PER
@calisuzi JJ B-PER
@UltyDiscGirl JJ B-PER
@BrownEquusrn NN B-PER
@Mindlessrobot37 JJ B-PER
I'll PRP O
never JJ O
watch VB O
that NN O
movie NN O
again DT O
I PRP O
cried JJ O
so NN O
hard NN O

Bruh NNP O
who NN O
wants VB O
to NN O
go NN O
to NN O
chipotle JJ B-ORG

Love NNP O
me NN O
a DT O
chicken JJ O
shawarma NN O
😍😍 NN O

Just NNP O
kicked NN O
Ryan NNP B-PER
in NN O
the NN O
balls VB O
and DT O
he NN O
hasn't VB O
moved NN O
in NN O
9 CD O
minutes NN O

It's PRP O
been NN O
7 CD O
months NN O
since NN O
I PRP O
cut NNS O
the NN O
hell NN O
out JJ O
of NN O
my NN O
hair NN O
and DT O
removed NN O
all DT O
the NN O
straight NN O
ends NN O

@justinbbradford JJ B-PER
it's JJ O
funny JJ O
because NN O
it's JJ O
bigger NN O
than NN O
a DT O
normal RB O
hat VB O
http//tco/NpUUX32chQ NN O

HA NNP O
Just NNP O
as DT O
well NN O

@beerandbutthole NN B-PER
you're NN O
beautiful NN O

@MJP1227 JJ B-PER
Thanks NNP O
Luv NNP O
Miss NNP O
ya NN O

When NNP O
your NN O
storage NN O
on NN O
your NN O
phone NN O
is NN O
almost DT O
full JJ O
and DT O
you NN O
have VB O
to NN O
delete NN O
all DT O
your NN O
Nash NNP B-PER
pictures NN O
http//tco/ZFSWx7IFXv NN O

Focus NNP O
on NN O
Product NNP O
http//tco/XtnrG9X8rg NN O

Cards VB O
against DT O
humanity NN O
😂👍 NN O

Kate NNP B-PER
McKinnon NNP I-PER
tho NN O
#mycalvins # O
#SNL # B-MISC

SAI IN O

Who NNP O
won NN O
on NN O
Friday NNP O
San VB B-LOC
Fernando NNP I-LOC
or NN O
van NN B-LOC
nuys JJ I-LOC
in NN O
basketball VB O

Sometimes NNP O
you NN O
gotta NN O
say VB O
look NN O
bitch NN O
you're NN O
not JJ O
getting NN O
in NN O
my NN O
butthole NN O

BULLSHIT NNP O
@alexandergold VB B-PER
SHUT NNP O
THE NNP O
FUCK NNP O
UP NNP O
BUGGER NNP O
OFF NNP O
FUCK NNP O
OFF NNP O
INFINITE PRP O
GOD NNP O
DAMN NNP O
@alexandergold VB B-PER

I'm PRP O
at DT O
Marcus NNP B-ORG
Orland NNP I-ORG
Park VB I-ORG
Cinema NNP I-ORG
- : O
@marcus_theatres JJ B-ORG
for NN O
American DT B-MISC
Sniper NNP I-MISC
in NN O
Orland NNP B-LOC
Park VB I-LOC
IL PRP I-LOC
https//tco/LLz6hWoLpc NN O

Big NNP O
ass DT O
sleepover NN O
tn NN O
hella NN O
food JJ O
✊👌 NN O

Two NNP O
of NN O
every NN O
human's NN O
favorite VB O
thing NN O
food JJ O
and DT O
sex NN O
http//tco/LX5Sjg2bq2 NN O

Our NNP O
party NN O
was VB O
lit NN O
till NN O
12 CD O
came VB O
😔 NN O

http//tco/YQPToklY1J NN O

@__TheRealLife JJ B-PER
I PRP O
love NN O
you NN O
too NN O
baby NN O
🙈💙🙌 JJ O

I PRP O
hate VB O
being NN O
the NN O
first NN O
person NN O
to NN O
text NN O
because NN O
I PRP O
don't NN O
want VB O
to NN O
be NN O
annoying DT O
🙈 NN O

@catiyas JJ O
is NN O
he NN O
rooting NN O
for NN O
the NN O
wrong NN O
kind NN O
of NN O
football JJ O
team NN O

@vinopa4me JJ B-PER
that's NN O
what NN O
I PRP O
thought NN O
n NN O
this NN O
game VB O
is NN O
funny JJ O
imagine NN O
how NN O
we NN O
feel JJ O
but NN O
then NN O
again DT O
imagine NN O
Dallas NNP B-ORG
players NN O
watchingcan't VB O
fathom VB O
it NN O

@AudreygurlAmy VB B-PER
@rascalflatts NN B-PER
I❤️them PRP O
too NN O
They NNP O
have VB O
a DT O
similar NN O
music NN O
vibe NN O
to NN O
someone NN O
else NN O
we NN O
love😉🎵👱 NN O
One NNP O
of NN O
faves VB O
is NN O
My NNP B-MISC
Wish NNP I-MISC

Why NNP O
is NN O
@VirginAmerica JJ B-ORG
like NN O
a DT O
dodgy NN O
disco NN O
in NN O
Leeds NNP B-LOC
http//tco/gL8BuyFcgl NN O

Way WRB O
to NN O
go NN O
matthews😘😘💚💚💛💛 VB O

@andersoncooper VB B-PER
You NNP O
lost NN O
Big NNP O
Fan NNP O
when NN O
Sara VB B-PER
Knight NNP I-PER
was VB O
murdered NN O
Allegan DT B-LOC
Co NNP I-LOC
MI NNP I-LOC
#Fugitive # O
Butch NNP O
Armed&DangerousRunning DT O
09Subaru CD O
#PrayJustice # O

it's JJ O
been NN O
a DT O
good NN O
day VB O

@OpTic_MBoZe JJ B-PER
party NN O
foul JJ O
$B $ O
http//tco/vMrw6jiL3m NN O

What NNP O
a DT O
comeback NNS O
Seahawks NNP B-ORG

They're NNP O
gonna NN O
cut NNS O
him NN O
immediately JJ O
lmao NN O
http//tco/UhA0xAfZF2 NN O

Almost DT O
time NN O
to NN O
put NN O
a DT O
beating NN O
on NN O
these NN O
Colt NNP B-ORG
boys NN O

My NNP O
mom NN O
moved NN O
to NN O
Seattle NNP B-LOC
when NN O
she NN O
was VB O
18 CD O
I PRP O
was VB O
born NN O
there NN O
and DT O
lived NN O
there NN O
for NN O
6 CD O
years NN O
and DT O
I'm PRP O
glad NN O
I PRP O
grew NN O
up JJ O
a DT O
Seattle NNP B-LOC
fan VB O
💙💚 NN O

👧💕 NN O
http//tco/29tq1vzul1 NN O

@_jakevalenti JJ B-PER
@kaitlynbrandt NN B-PER
me NN O
& CC O
Hannah NNP B-PER
r NN O
supposed NN O
to NN O
be NN O
going NN O
out JJ O

@GarettSmith23 NN B-PER
bc NN O
you NN O
don't NN O
wanna VB O
loose NN O
in NN O
rummy NN O

Anyone DT O
want VB O
to NN O
hangout VB O

@natharsis NN B-PER
if NN O
we NN O
date VB O
i'm NN O
grabbing NN O
that NN O
ass DT O
whenever NN O
i NN O
want VB O
idc NN O
yes NN O
pls NN O

@m00ngoddess JJ B-PER
miss NN O
u NN O
too NN O
😚 NN O

Can VB O
Russell NNP B-PER
fly JJ O
out JJ O
to NN O
Foxboro NNP B-LOC
fast VB O
enough NN O

@code_red_24 JJ B-PER
winners NN O
go NN O
for NN O
it NN O

Idk PRP O
how NN O
ppl NN O
can VB O
watch VB O
football JJ O

@OGKeithSweat JJ B-PER
miss- NN O
b NN O
Yeskeithsweat NNP B-PER

@StevenLacy JJ B-PER
they NN O
don't NN O
call VB O
it NN O
day VB O
of NN O
rest NN O
4 CD O
nothinglol JJ O

@adebukola_xoxo VB B-PER
Well NNP O
change NNS O
the NN O
station NN O

I PRP O
didn't NN O
know NN O
in NN O
college NNS O
I PRP O
would NN O
be NN O
Steven NNP B-PER
glansberging NN O
so NN O
often JJ O
lol NN O
@C_Callinan JJ B-PER

@alaghaarts3 VB B-PER
Thanks NNP O
for NN O
following JJ O
- : O

Shout NNP O
out JJ O
to NN O
my NN O
patriots VB O
I PRP O
Love NNP O
yall VB O
Super NNP O
Bowl NNP O
Baby NNP O

Yes NNP O
http//tco/sl6f2K7R7B NN O

How NNP O
can VB O
you NN O
call VB O
yourself NN O
a DT O
mother NN O
You NNP O
can't VB O
even NN O
call VB O
your NN O
son NN O
on NN O
his NN O
birthday NN O
You NNP O
are DT O
a DT O
sorry NN O
excuse NN O
of NN O
a DT O
parent NN O
#worthless # O

When NNP O
my NN O
grandparents NN O
comment NNS O
on NN O
my NN O
insta NN O
picture NN O
because NN O
is NN O
said VB O
I PRP O
love NN O
you NN O
❤️ NN O
http//tco/bJPNv6aDfR NN O

@CraziestSex NN O
@xo_najahh JJ B-PER
but NN O
i'm NN O
the NN O
emotional NN O
one😒 JJ O

@sallythatgurll NN B-PER
Sthu NNP O
RT NNP O
@keeraGOONETTE JJ O
Taking VB O
it NN O
slow NN O
>>> JJ O
Taking VB O
it NN O
nowhere JJ O
u NN O
must NN O
be NN O
a DT O
GB NNP O
fan VB O
with NN O
that NN O
tudey NN O
😂 NN O

Brian NNP B-PER
done NN O
fucked JJ O
up JJ O
I PRP O
wouldn't NN O
even NN O
said VB O
that NN O
😂😂 NN O

@StacyDavisIV JJ B-PER
@thathooperchris JJ B-PER
hah VB O
never JJ O
am DT O
i NN O
see NN O
you NN O
out JJ O
there NN O
doing NN O
yo NN O
thang NN O
though NN O

I'm PRP O
about DT O
to NN O
murder NN O
chicken JJ O
nachos RB O

LA VB B-LOC
baby NN O
@ NN O
Los NNP B-ORG
Angeles DT I-ORG
International PRP I-ORG
Airport DT I-ORG
LAX VB I-ORG
- : O
@flylaxairport JJ O
in NN O
Los NNP B-LOC
Angeles DT I-LOC
CA VB I-LOC
https//tco/2T91YcAgaG NN O

Only NNP O
thing NN O
I'm PRP O
looking NN O
forward NN O
to NN O
tomorrow NN O
is NN O
6th CD O
period NN O

Afternoon DT O
rain VB O
today NN O
high NN O
71 CD O
22 CD O
C SYM O

@demas_emmett JJ B-PER
hey NN O
you NN O
wanna VB O
see NN O
a DT O
picture NN O
of NN O
me NN O
eating VB O
a DT O
banana VB O

Dang NNP O
I PRP O
missed NN O
his NN O
call VB O

RIP NN O
Stuart NNP B-PER
Scott NNP I-PER
he NN O
will NN O
always DT O
be NN O
as DT O
cool NNS O
as DT O
the NN O
other JJ O
side NN O
of NN O
the NN O
pillow NN O

Kinda NNP O
wanted VB O
to NN O
go NN O
to NN O
the NN O
mall VB O
today NN O
soo NN O

I'm PRP O
tired NN O
¤ NN O

Follow NNP O
@L7Chills JJ B-PER
He's NNP O
a DT O
great NN O
person NN O
has VB O
a DT O
cool NNS O
accent DT O
and DT O
is NN O
a DT O
fucking JJ O
amaaazing DT O
trickshotter NN O
<3 $ O

Other NNP O
than NN O
that NN O
I PRP O
say VB O
mother NN O
of NN O
my NN O
child JJ O

I'm PRP O
at DT O
The NNP B-ORG
Yoga NNP I-ORG
Room NNP I-ORG
in NN O
Astoria DT B-LOC
NY NNP I-LOC
https//tco/CDDC2KpZh2 NN O

@nick_medley21 JJ B-PER
@evie_lawson JJ B-PER
why NN O
the NN O
sad VB O
face VB O

Why NNP O
do NN O
I PRP O
even NN O
try NN O
to NN O
be NN O
happy VB O
anymore DT O

👈 NN O
bold NN O
AF DT O
Shit NNP O
I've PRP O
hit NN O
on NN O
friends JJ O
& CC O
turned NN O
around DT O
& CC O
see NN O
the NN O
other JJ O
friend JJ O
dolly NN O
& CC O
still JJ O
said VB O
some NN O
creep NNS O
shit NN O
& CC O
had VB O
her NN O
hype NN O
IDGAF PRP O

@JimGaffigan JJ B-PER
#SEEK2015 # B-MISC
is NN O
ready NN O
for NN O
ya NN O

If PRP O
she's NN O
sayin VB O
you've NN O
changed NNS O
maybe VB O
you NN O
just NN O
grew NN O
up JJ O
and DT O
they NN O
stayed NN O
young NN O
and DT O
immature JJ O

#IMO # O
People NNP O
taking VB O
this NN O
melanin NN O
shit NN O
too NN O
far VB O
We NNP O
got NN O
the NN O
science JJ O
we NN O
know NN O
the NN O
hidden NN O
truths NN O
etcwhat NN O
the NN O
fuck JJ O
is NN O
being NN O
done NN O
tho NN O

And DT O
if NN O
you NN O
knew NN O
how NN O
proud NN O
I PRP O
was VB O
you'd NN O
never JJ O
shed NN O
a DT O
tear NN O
have VB O
a DT O
fear NN O
no NNS O
you NN O
wldn't NN O
do NN O
that NN O
& CC O
no NNS O
I PRP O
didnt NN O
pick NN O
the NN O
day VB O
to NN O
turn NN O
a DT O
page VB O
💔💔🎶🎵 JJ O

@nickthegod__ JJ B-PER
yes NN O

night NN O
class NNS O
night NN O
class NNS O
😑 NN O

My NNP O
pops NN O
is NN O
my NN O
world NN O
🌎👨💙 JJ O

*looks JJ O
at DT O
amount DT O
of NN O
homework NN O
left NN O
dies NN O
on NN O
the NN O
inside* NN O

@Hermann22 NN B-PER
Just NNP O
look NN O
at DT O
Star NNP O
Tours NNP O
Rebels NNP O
and DT O
the NN O
Phineas NNP O
and DT O
Ferb NNP O
crossover NNS O
All DT O
really NN O
well NN O
done NN O

Bouta NNP O
have VB O
someone NN O
bring NN O
me NN O
something NN O
to NN O
eat VB O

Watch WRB O
the NN O
loss NN O

@CraveMyThoughts NN O
They're NNP O
were NN O
the NN O
best NN O
part NN O
of NN O
gossip NN B-ORG
girl NN I-ORG
😭❤ NN O
http//tco/6mPTVrN9u3 NN O

Santa VB B-LOC
Barbara IN I-LOC
is NN O
where NN O
it's JJ O
at DT O
🙌 NN O

@Dflocka_Byrd JJ B-PER
@sweetteaislife JJ B-PER
im NN O
crushin NNS O
@👀 NN O

Exhausted NNP O
😴😴 NN O

I PRP O
usually JJ O
just NN O
call VB O
you NN O
babe NN O
because NN O
it's JJ O
only JJ O
one JJ O
syllable NN O
@__CodyP JJ B-PER

BETTER NNP O
BEING NNP O
THAT NNP O
ITS PRP O
MORE NNP O
DURABLE NNP O
AND DT O
STILL NNP O
FUNCTIONS NNP O
THE NNP O
WAY WRB O
IT PRP O
WAS WRB O
INTENDED PRP O
TO NNP O

I PRP O
need JJ O
more NN O
hot NN O
boys NN O
in NN O
my NN O
life NN O

i NN O
hate VB O
@__samfa JJ B-PER
and DT O
her NN O
mom NN O
😒 NN O

@cherylLconnors JJ B-PER
you NN O
and DT O
Brit NNP B-PER
look NN O
like NN O
porcelain NN O
dolls NN O
in NN O
your NN O
icon JJ O

smooth JJ O
like NN O
that NN O
henney NN O

@darsaayboogotee NN B-PER
okay NN O
just NN O
tell NN O
me NN O
when NN O
💁 NN O

Grown NNP O
folks JJ O
gospel NN O
Nawwww NNP O
smh JJ O

It's PRP O
this NN O
one JJ O
thing NN O
that's NN O
got NN O
me NN O
trippin NN O

god NN B-MISC
how NN O
did NN O
i NN O
ever NN O
like NN O
you NN O

@iM_DopeAs123 NN B-PER
😂😂😂 JJ O
better NN O
get NN O
to NN O
it NN O
🔬🔭🔎🏇 JJ O

@NicoleDemarest JJ B-PER
wtf NN O
why NN O
didn't NN O
you NN O
say VB O
hey NN O
bitch NN O

I PRP O
swear NN O
if NN O
they NN O
play NN O
some NN O
dry NN O
ass DT O
stale NN O
beats NN O
at DT O
sweet NN O
16 CD O
I'm PRP O
hookin NN O
up JJ O
an DT O
aux DT O
taking VB O
the NN O
joint NN O
over JJ O

This NNP O
has VB O
been NN O
the NN O
best NN O
Christmas NNP B-MISC
break NN O
ever NN O
Got NNP O
to NN O
hangout VB O
with NN O
some NN O
awsome DT O
ppl NN O
and DT O
had VB O
some NN O
great NN O
presents NN O
Back IN O
to NN O
work NN O
tomorrow NN O
$$😎 $ O

First NNP O
lunch NN O
is NN O
always DT O
lame NN O
lol NN O

Stop NNP O
with NN O
chicken JJ O
nuggets JJ O
Can VB O
no NNS O
female JJ O
cook NNS O
an DT O
actual DT O
chicken JJ O
and DT O
make NN O
a DT O
healthy NN O
meal NN O
other JJ O
than NN O
me NN O
Bitches NNP O
go NN O
take VB O
a DT O
cooking NNS O
class NNS O

And DT O
bring NN O
on NN O
the NN O
seizures JJ O

@GrizzGod77 NN B-PER
#IfWeDate # O
I'm PRP O
in NN O
it NN O
for NN O
the NN O
long NN O
run NN O
I'm PRP O
over JJ O
games VB O
I'm PRP O
ready NN O
to NN O
settle NN O
down👌 NN O
I've PRP O
been NN O
over JJ O
games VB O

oh NN O
well NN O
then NN O

Less NNP O
than NN O
six NN O
months NN O
left NN O
with NN O
the NN O
people NN O
who NN O
have VB O
defined NN O
the NN O
last NN O
four JJ O
years NN O
am DT O
I PRP O
the NN O
only JJ O
one JJ O
who NN O
thinks NN O
thats NN O
insane NN O

Bet NNP O
oakman IN B-PER
won't NN O
fight NN O
Craig NNP B-PER
he NN O
saw VB O
what NN O
he NN O
did NN O
to NN O
deebo NN B-PER
he NN O
ain't DT O
stupid NN O
smh JJ O
😴 NN O

@riversg_lm JJ O
sólo NN O
tengo NN O
algo DT O
que NN O
decir NN O
esta NN O
madrugada VB O
tu NN O
y NN O
yo NN O
siempre NN O
juntos NN O
jajajaja NN O
eres NN O
como NNS O
Seth NNP O
Rogen NNP O
jajaja NN O
http//tco/dLrbbQClDM NN O

Its PRP O
like NN O
2am CD O
and DT O
I PRP O
have VB O
school JJ O
tomorrow NN O
I PRP O
cant VB O
fucking JJ O
sleep NN O
#killmenow # O

Lord NNP B-MISC
knows NN O
I PRP O
can't VB O
complain NNS O
cause VB O
even NN O
if NN O
I PRP O
do NN O
it NN O
feels JJ O
the NN O
saaaaame VB O

Likewise NNP O

I'm PRP O
m NN O
going NN O
to NN O
school JJ O
now JJ O
I'll PRP O
talk VB O
to NN O
yall VB O
later NN O

Children's NNP O
hospital NN O
😋 NN O
no NNS O
school JJ O

The NNP O
Sam VB B-PER
smith JJ I-PER
cd NNS O
really NN O
does NN O
ya NN O
in NN O

@Cinedaze JJ O
This NNP O
may VB O
be NN O
the NN O
apparently DT O
region-free NN O
DVD NNP O
from JJ O
Korea NNP B-LOC

Another DT O
sure NN O
fire NN O
way VB O
to NN O
get NN O
out JJ O
of NN O
work NN O
http//tco/Ybypl4G22p NN O

Lmao NNP O
now JJ O
she's NN O
deff NN O
all DT O
me NN O
😂😍 NN O
http//tco/IZqbsf2ayC NN O

@TeamKenyaFans JJ O
@__Bonafide JJ O
@ariannataken VB O
Tweet NNP O
was VB O
deleted NN O

@samknovels NN B-PER
@AngelaAckerman VB B-PER
scene JJ O
& CC O
sequel NN O
can VB O
do NN O
so NN O
much NN O
to NN O
help NN O
take VB O
instinct NN O
to NN O
technique NN O
for NN O
writers NN O
struggling NN O
with NN O
pacing VB O
& CC O
plot NN O

😘😘😘😬 JJ O
oh NN O
she NN O
single NN O
http//tco/7ih3r6fBwG NN O

@lisasy JJ B-PER
Also DT O
added DT O
@disqus JJ O
so NN O
feel JJ O
free JJ O
to NN O
leave NN O
comments NNS O

please NN O
tag VB O
your NN O
opinions IN O
as DT O
wrong NN O

@LeDivaJosa JJ B-PER
@madimann38 JJ B-PER
@LeDivaJosa JJ B-PER
Don't NNP O
like NN O
when NN O
people NN O
text NN O
back VB O
when NN O
they NN O
feel JJ O
like NN O
it👀😳yea NN O
mf😅😂😂 NN O

@TipSosa JJ B-PER
@_____Marrrri JJ B-PER
@thatbomb_ JJ B-PER
bye NN O
snitch JJ O
😒 NN O

I'm PRP O
at DT O
I-40 PRP O
west NN O
rest NN O
area DT O
in NN O
Ozark NNP B-LOC
AR DT I-LOC
https//tco/7XsKNAteaz NN O

I'm PRP O
just NN O
happy VB O
because NN O
the NN O
bachelor VB O
comes NNS O
on NN O
tonight NN O

@jameswoodmotors JJ O
I'll PRP O
check NNS O
you NN O
guys NN O
out JJ O
next JJ O
month NN O

Dinnah NNP O
at DT O
@KellysRoastBeef JJ B-ORG
in NN O
Medford NNP B-LOC
MA NNP I-LOC
https//tco/BAzJFDGnFM NN O

🌕🌕🌕 JJ O
<---- SYM O
those NN O
are DT O
pupusa NN O
emojis NN O
😎 NN O
@ NN O
Oasis IN B-PER
Pupuseria NNP I-PER
http//tco/btW2H8h3im NN O

i NN O
know NN O
alot DT O
of NN O
people NN O
talk VB O
about DT O
me NN O
but NN O
they NN O
aint DT O
gon NN O
be NN O
straight NN O
up JJ O
& CC O
say VB O
it NN O
in NN O
my NN O
face VB O

@QuanDaDon_ JJ B-PER
@beauteRebelle_x NN B-PER
@thtdamnDES JJ B-PER
😂😂😂😂 JJ O
lol NN O
It PRP O
is NN O
we NN O
better NN O
than NN O
everyone NN O
else NN O
💁 NN O
true NN O
true NN O
💁👐 NN O
proceed NN O

The NNP O
cool NNS O
thing NN O
about DT O
being NN O
at DT O
home NN O
is NN O
that NN O
if NN O
I PRP O
don't NN O
do NN O
something NN O
for NN O
long NN O
enough NN O
someone NN O
else NN O
will NN O
do NN O
it NN O
for NN O
me NN O

apush DT O
is NN O
already DT O
OC NNP O
this NN O
semester NN O

It's PRP O
officially JJ O
that NN O
time NN O
of NN O
year NN O
when NN O
those NN O
meme NN O
like NN O
valentines NN B-MISC
day VB I-MISC
cards VB O
appear DT O
on NN O
twitter NN B-ORG

@VelentineCards JJ O
http//tco/6mCkJWWxMT NN O
@ImAdamRyan NN B-PER

@kennyfreeman4 JJ B-PER
@antijokeapple VB B-PER
How NNP O
to NN O
put NN O
on NN O
jeans NN O
Step NNP O
1 CD O
put NN O
on NN O
leggings NN O
@ClaudiaJanex3 JJ B-PER
hahah VB O

You NNP O
Gotta NNP O
Tell NNP O
Her NNP O
Look NNP O
I PRP O
Wanna WRB O
Fuck NNP O
I PRP O
Like NNP O
You NNP O
But NNP O
I PRP O
Wanna WRB O
Fuck NNP O
Because NNP O
If PRP O
It's PRP O
Wack WRB O
Af DT O
I'll PRP O
Have NNP O
To NNP O
Reevaluate NNP O
You NNP O
💀💀💀💀 JJ O

@Justin_Renoo JJ B-PER
😭 NN O

@lexysavvides JJ B-PER
yep NN O
I'm PRP O
familiar VB O
with NN O
zink NN O
Do NNP O
they NN O
also DT O
take VB O
ages DT O
to NN O
print NN O
- : O

#BringBackOurClassyGirls2015 # O

I PRP O
really NN O
almost DT O
texted NN O
a DT O
whole NN O
essay NN O
and DT O
then NN O
I PRP O
just NN O
deleted NN O
the NN O
whole NN O
thing NN O
😩 NN O

@skylor_black NN B-PER
always DT O
the NN O
right NN O
time NN O

$20 $ O
for NN O
$50 $ O
Certificate NNP O
at DT O
Prodigy NNP B-ORG
Moving NNP I-ORG
http//tco/f3txeZLJVb NN O

lol NN O
still JJ O
drunk NN O
lol NN O
summatives NN O
fuck JJ O
lol NN O

Michael NNP B-PER
from JJ O
5sos CD O
please NN O
follow JJ O
me NN O
so NN O
I PRP O
can VB O
start NN O
the NN O
new JJ O
year NN O
happy VB O
💓🍆🔮 JJ O
@Michael5SOS JJ B-PER
3191 CD I-PER

@MMekus17 JJ B-PER
your NN O
shoe NN O
is NN O
dirty NN O

Randle VB B-PER
inna NN O
cut😈✨😂❤️ NNS O
http//tco/dpcfdX3Xa5 NN O

Happy NNP O
PLL NNP O
Day NNP O

When NNP O
he NN O
was VB O
little NN O
he NN O
used JJ O
to NN O
play NN O
with NN O
his NN O
willy NN O
like NN O
he NN O
was VB O
playing NN O
with NN O
a DT O
rambunctious VB O
puppy NN O

@becccajoanne NN B-PER
YES NNP O
ME NNP O
AND DT O
TIANNA NNP O
ARE DT O

Court NNP O
today NN O
#freeskyler # O

srsly NN O
someone NN O
answer DT O
😭😭 NN O

@hillydilly JJ B-PER
urgh JJ O
fine NN O
just NN O
hurrrrrry NN O
<3 $ O
u NN O

tryna NN O
hit NN O
a DT O
long NN O
route NN O
after DT O
work NN O
need JJ O
it NN O

queen NN B-PER
really NN O
been NN O
working NN O
all DT O
day VB O
im NN O
proud NN O
of NN O
this NN O
bitch NN O

@_WEluvAlbee JJ B-PER
dm NN O
me NN O
that NN O
picture NN O
I PRP O
took NN O
in NN O
your NN O
phone NN O

El NN O
viejo NN O
truco NN O
de NN O
sumergir NN O
la NN O
rosca NN O
justo NN O
después NN O
de NN O
cortarla NNS O
#oremosportodoslosmuñecosahogados # O
#yamecansedecomer # O
http//tco/mCkItmthLj NN O

@Vortaenig JJ O
omg JJ O
I PRP O
re NN O
take VB O
some NN O
more NN O
pic NN O
in NN O
the NN O
dark VB O
this NN O
is NN O
what NN O
I PRP O
saw VB O
http//tco/Go68OlrxVe NN O

all DT O
my NN O
classes NNS O
for NN O
tomorrow NN O
were NN O
cancelled VB O
😂 NN O

It's PRP O
crazy NNS O
one JJ O
text NN O
can VB O
literally NN O
make NN O
someone's NN O
mood NN O
so NN O
much NN O
better NN O

@Ms_Arri JJ B-PER
@Genji_Montana JJ B-PER
I PRP O
hope NN O
everything NN O
good NN O
with NN O
u NN O
& CC O
the NN O
family VB O
Thank NNP O
u NN O
Arri DT B-PER
Keep NNP O
us JJ O
in NN O
Prayers NNP O
and DT O
Let NNP O
God NNP O

S/O NNP O
to NN O
that NN O
kid NN O
you NN O
use JJ O
to NN O
be NN O

i NN O
use JJ O
to NN O
want VB O
the NN O
world NN O
now JJ O
i NN O
just NN O
want VB O
the NN O
good NN O
pieces NN O

@sabrinarangel33 NN B-PER
so😘 NN O

Better NNP O
yet NN O
I'm PRP O
going NN O
with NN O
my NN O
little NN O
big NN O
😌 NN O

FLY NNP O
OH NNP O
MY NNP O
IT'S PRP O
ALIL DT O
BIT NNP O
SCARY NNP O

Everyone NNP O
always DT O
snapchats NN O
me NN O
when NN O
I PRP O
look NN O
like NN O
a DT O
troll NN O
But NNP O
when NN O
I PRP O
look NN O
decent NN O
nobody JJ O
does NN O
l NN O
o NN O
l NN O

@TylerGonzales23 JJ B-PER
oh NN O
I PRP O
know NN O
I PRP O
was VB O
just NN O
saying VB O
it NN O
can VB O
go NN O
both NN O
ways VB O

SWV NNP B-MISC
Reunited NNP I-MISC
comes NNS O
back VB O
on NN O
tomorrow NN O

Faaaakkkkeeeee NNP O
That's NNP O
how NN O
you NN O
spell NN O
it NN O
💯 NN O

Love NNP O
has VB O
a DT O
nasty RB O
habit NN O
of NN O
disappearing NN O
overnight JJ O

@chxmv JJ O
I PRP O
lowkey NN O
forgot NN O
bout NN O
this NN O
ha NN O

Hey NNP O
@CNN JJ B-ORG
all DT O
I PRP O
see NN O
with NN O
those NN O
robotic NN O
bartenders NN O
is NN O
lost NN O
American DT B-MISC
jobs NN O
Thanks NNP O
for NN O
that NN O
#CNNNYE # B-ORG
#fb # B-ORG

@DinahBlueCarter JJ B-PER
about DT O
me NN O

*waits NN O
for NN O
J NN B-PER
cole NNS I-PER
to NN O
make NN O
2015 CD B-MISC
Forest NNP I-MISC
Hills NNP I-MISC
Drive* NNP I-MISC

Glad NNP O
bae VB O
is NN O
okay NN O
✊❤️ JJ O

The NNP O
Sunday NNP O
Propers NNP O
Feast NNP O
Thy NNP O
Most NNP O
Holy NNP O
Name NNP O
http//tco/3ZGQuUwJMq NN O
http//tco/euGWxdT7M8 NN O

My NNP O
job NN O
basically VB O
consists NNS O
of NN O
me NN O
watching VB O
sports NN O
all DT O
day VB O

I'm PRP O
so NN O
irritated NN O

Mall NNP O
later NN O

Wind NNP O
7 CD O
mph NN O
W NN O
Barometer IN O
2991 CD O
in NN O
Falling NNP O
Temperature NNP O
334 CD O
°F NN O
Rain VB O
today NN O
000 CD O
in NN O
Humidity NNP O
54% CD O

Not NNP O
liking NN O
the NN O
Billy NNP B-PER
Idol PRP I-PER
hate VB O
I'm PRP O
seeing NN O
on NN O
my NN O
TL NNP O

I PRP O
got NN O
50 CD O
on NN O
Oregon NNP B-LOC

#dogs # O
#life # O
I PRP O
don't NN O
want VB O
to NN O
be NN O
touched NN O
by NN O
#nobody # O
@ NN O
Hyatt NNP B-ORG
Regency NNP I-ORG
Jersey NNP I-ORG
City NNP I-ORG
http//tco/cKpKumtK7h NN O

@RajonRondo NN B-PER
your NN O
my NN O
favorite VB O
happy VB O
new JJ O
year NN O
☺️ NN O

@Siennerrr JJ B-PER
Oh NNP O
my NN O
gosh NN O
Ashley DT B-PER
came VB O
in NN O
clutch NNS O
last NN O
night NN O
with NN O
that NN O
crab NNS O
soup NN O
😩👌🙌 JJ O
cream NNS O
or NN O
md NN O

This NNP O
year NN O
of NN O
music NN O
is NN O
going NN O
to NN O
be NN O
great NN O

So NNP O
do NN O
I PRP O
gotta NN O
start NN O
getting NN O
ready NN O
orrrrrr NN O
Should NNP O
I PRP O
just NN O
take VB O
a DT O
fcking JJ O
nap RB O
Nigga NNP O
let NN O
me NN O
know NN O

I PRP O
cant VB O
believe NN O
he NN O
was VB O
right# NN O

@socialscandal JJ B-PER
no NNS O
im NN O
in NN O
times NN O
Square NNP O

#Noles # O

@floridastate JJ B-PER
has VB O
officially JJ O
given NN O
up JJ O

I PRP O
feel JJ O
like NN O
a DT O
Seminole NNP B-MISC
tears NN O
# # O
might NN O
be NN O
innapropriate NN O
here NN O

@MommyUnit JJ B-MISC
this NN O
one JJ O
started NN O
yelling NN O
at DT O
me NN O
couldn't NNS O
avoid DT O
it NN O

LOOK NNP O
AT DT O
THE NNP O
MOON NNP O
GO NNP O
OUTSIDE NNP O

@RushDeron JJ B-PER
http//tco/k3ZjqGPgiZ NN O

@treezelic NN O
👌👌😂😂😂 JJ O
@GrumpyAssCat NN B-MISC
Meanwhile NNP O
http//tco/o4NkiJjcui NN O

I PRP O
hate VB O
that NN O
McDonalds NNP B-ORG
and DT O
I PRP O
hate VB O
you NN O
too NN O
Christina NNP B-PER
@eriicaa_xoxo NN B-PER
@jesssiiimarie JJ B-PER
@jeffyd4life JJ B-PER

Going NNP O
into NN O
2015 CD O
with NN O
a DT O
big NN O
smile JJ O
like NN O
this☺️ NN O
@ThekidPmillz JJ B-PER
http//tco/mbxOOjhpiI NN O

We NNP O
back VB O
in NN O
this NN O

Def NNP O
not JJ O
in NN O
shape NN O
for NN O
soccer NN O

Keep NNP O
it NN O
up JJ O
Ohio NNP B-ORG
state NN I-ORG
🙏🙏🙌 JJ O
Oregon NNP B-ORG
vs NN O
Ohio NNP B-ORG
state NN I-ORG
would NN O
be NN O
a DT O
great NN O
game VB O
🏈🏈🏈 JJ O

@JRJTALKER NN B-PER
I PRP O
want VB O
to NN O
kiss NN O
his NN O
sweet NN O
face VB O

HuffPost NNP O
Religion's NNP O
People NNP O
Of NNP O
The NNP O
Year NNP O
Religious NNP O
Leaders NNP O
Of NNP O
#Ferguson # O
http//tco/K3LY84fYre NN O
via NN O
@HuffPostRelig NN O
http//tco/4koy7JLKux NN O

Helllllll NNP O
yeaaaaa NN O
buckeyes NN O
😏 NN O

@AMiliner_5 VB B-PER
shh NN O

@Beanie_Niall NN B-PER
@drummerftstyles NN B-PER
16 CD O
in NN O
May NNP O
hbu NN O
http//tco/lWEjfH7pFp NN O
16 CD O
in NN O
August17 DT O
in NN O
july NN O

Bedtime NNP O
so NN O
cue NNS O
crazy NNS O
foot JJ O
pain IN O
so NN O
I PRP O
can't VB O
sleep NN O
Not NNP O
like NN O
this NN O
hasn't VB O
happened VB O
the NN O
last NN O
8 CD O
nights NN O
in NN O
a DT O
row NN O
#imisssleep # O

Prayers NNP O
for NN O
@joshuasmith1535 JJ B-PER
when NN O
I PRP O
turn NN O
21 CD O

I've PRP O
driven NN O
150 CD O
miles NN O
since NN O
10 CD O
am DT O
help NN O

What NNP O
is NN O
a DT O
milf NN O

@KayOthee NN B-PER
whit NN O
was VB O
I PRP O
saying VB O

#Nursing # O
#Job # O
in NN O
#FortScott # B-LOC
KS NNP O
Registered NNP O
Nurse NNP O
at DT O
Mercy NNP B-ORG
Health NNP I-ORG
http//tco/AZOHDOrIkx NN O
#VeteranJob # O
#Jobs # O
#TweetMyJobs # O

Because NNP O
moving NN O
trash NN O
cans VB O
and DT O
tables VB O
out JJ O
the NN O
way VB O
for NN O
our NN O
mats VB O
is NN O
exactly NN O
what NN O
I PRP O
wanted VB O
to NN O
do NN O
at DT O
900 CD O
in NN O
the NN O
morning NN O
😤 NN O

@ComeTo_BRIzil JJ B-PER
😍 NN O

Today NNP O
I PRP O
will NN O
achieve DT O
what NN O
I PRP O
want#Pow#Winner#Paid#Sistas VB O

let's NN O
now JJ O
imagine NN O
Beyonce NNP B-PER
belting NN O
over JJ O
the NN O
1-900-Hustler CD B-MISC
beat NN O

I PRP O
haven't VB O
ate DT O
REAL NNP O
food JJ O
since NN O
new JJ O
years NN O
eve NN O

I PRP O
hit NN O
my NN O
face VB O
on NN O
the NN O
floor JJ O
when NN O
I PRP O
tripped NN O
over JJ O
my NN O
luggage NN O
this NN O
morning NN O
😩 NN O

Teacher NNP O
alright DT O
you're NN O
dismissed NN O
Shawn NNP B-PER
Oakman IN I-PER
there NN O
was VB O
homework NN O
Students NNP O
yeah NN O
wtf NN O
we NN O
tryna NN O
get NN O
educated NN O
n NN O
shit NN O
http//tco/gF3wIAHVvH NN O

Trying NNP O
to NN O
figure NN O
this NN O
out JJ O

Broooo NNP O
this NN O
lady NN O
is NN O
being NN O
so NN O
rude NN O
😂 NN O

@itscoleharmon NN B-PER
What NNP O
it NN O
looks NN O
like NN O
to NN O
have VB O
sex NN O
with NN O
a DT O
girl NN O
over JJ O
5'10 CD O
http//tco/71tjliY5PF NN O
naw RB O
fr NN O

@ruslan_saleh_ JJ B-PER
she'd NN O
just NN O
call VB O
back VB O
and DT O
keep NN O
talking VB O

Liesss NNP O

If PRP O
AW DT O
believes NN O
in NN O
a DT O
player NN O
he NN O
plays NN O
him NN O
- : O
and DT O
very NN O
often JJ O
even NN O
when NN O
he's NN O
not JJ O
100% CD O
fit NN O

@SumireCarmel JJ B-PER
I've PRP O
been NN O
in NN O
town NN O
since NN O
last NN O
night NN O
I'll PRP O
be NN O
here NN O
till NN O
Sunday👏 NNP O

@railey_tassin4 NN B-PER
guys NN O
that NN O
are DT O
7'4-8'2 CD O
>>>>😩😩😩😍😍😍👌👌👌 JJ O
I'll PRP O
be NN O
as DT O
big NN O
as DT O
you NN O
need JJ O
me NN O
to NN O
be😏 NN O

we NN O
the NN O
best NN O
pushing NN O
haters VB O
to NN O
the NN O
left NN O
😈 NN O

It's PRP O
prob NN O
fun JJ O
being NN O
a DT O
spring NN O
hill NN O
thug NN O
lmao NN O
I PRP O
mean NN O
c'mon NNS O
it's JJ O
gotta NN O
be NN O
comical NNS O

I've PRP O
called VB O
animal DT O
control NNS O

Migraine NNP B-MISC
😔 NN O

I PRP O
like NN O
what NN O
I PRP O
like NN O
😏😏😏 JJ O

I PRP O
trust NN O
no NNS O
one JJ O

J NN B-PER
Cole NNP I-PER
x NN O
No NNP O
Role NNP O
Modelz🔥🙌 NNP O

@vincegenitals JJ B-PER
fine NN O
i NN O
dnt NN O
want VB O
u NN O
2 CD O
b NN O
my NN O
bf NN O
anymore'''''''''' DT O

Made NNP O
it NN O
home NN O
safe VB O
I PRP O
drive NN O
like NN O
a DT O
grandma NN O
in NN O
this NN O
weather NN O

Prolly NNP O
tweeted NN O
this NN O
before NN O
but NN O
the NN O
second NN O
drop NN O
to NN O
burial NN O
> NN O

Can't VB O
talk VB O
to NN O
a DT O
guy NN O
without NN O
people NN O
always DT O
thinking NN O
it's JJ O
more NN O

not JJ O
sure NN O
if NN O
I'm PRP O
gunna NN O
be NN O
able DT O
to NN O
sleep NN O
tonight NN O

@myab3_ JJ O
KML NNP O
NVM NNP O
ICANNT PRP O
FIND NNP O
IT PRP O
NOMOE NNP O

Dont NNP O
know NN O
if NN O
I'm PRP O
sad VB O
or NN O
pissed NN O
off JJ O

I PRP O
hate VB O
those NN O
people NN O
on NN O
Instagram PRP B-ORG
who NN O
think NN O
they're NN O
tumblr NN B-PER
and DT O
don't NN O
have VB O
any DT O
pictures NN O
of NN O
their NN O
face VB O
and DT O
post NN O
a DT O
lot NN O
but NN O
delete NN O
it NN O
after DT O

I PRP O
hope NN O
Kt NNP B-PER
replies NN O
asap DT O
im NN O
bored NN O

Strong NNP O
Fathers NNP O
Strong NNP O
Daughters NNP O
http//tco/c2u8GGSfqp NN O

MAH NNP O
MEN NNP O
♥ NN O
http//tco/4ZpB1hGDYo NN O

First NNP O
time NN O
wearing NN O
pants VB O
in NN O
9 CD O
days VB O
😭 NN O

Selling NNP O
the NN O
lebrons NN B-MISC
size NN O
11 CD O
dm NN O
me NN O
if NN O
interested NN O
http//tco/8lNqETV07I NN O

@iH8TvvitterHoes NN O
This NNP O
is NN O
the NN O
meaning NN O
of NN O
#FriendshipGoals # O
http//tco/ZIOZGfVRMh NN O
this NN O
would NN O
be NN O
us JJ O
@adalyns__mommy VB B-PER

Sitting NNP O
in NN O
on NN O
#AHA2015 # B-MISC
@SHARPorg JJ B-ORG
The NNP B-MISC
Practice NNP I-MISC
of NN I-MISC
Book NNP I-MISC
History NNP I-MISC
Between NNP I-MISC
and DT I-MISC
Beyond NNP I-MISC
Disciplines NNP I-MISC
http//tco/niOugxRHsj NN O

@GrandaddyJoel NN B-PER
💀💀💀 JJ O
RT NNP O
@ESP_Nique JJ B-PER
@caposatl JJ B-PER
😂😂 NN O
bruh NN O
http//tco/D00iv1AK5Q NN O
lmao NN O
that NN O
bitch NN O
look NN O
like NN O
a DT O
great NN O
Dane NNP O
BRUH NNP O

Knock NNP O
Knock NNP O
Whose NNP O
there NN O
Nash NNP O
Nash NNP O
who NN O
GO NNP O
WATCH WRB O
NASHS NNP B-PER
NEW NNP O
VIDEO NNP O
https//tco/kjSKV97SOO NN O
Its PRP O
so NN O
funny JJ O
@Nashgrier NN B-PER
#NashsNewYearsSkit # O
47 CD O

In PRP O
Harlem NNP B-LOC
rn NN O

@Caspar_Lee JJ B-PER
@biebswithcaylen NN B-PER
lol NN O

The NNP O
old JJ O
twenty NN O
dollar NN O
bills>>> NN O
http//tco/nVT3J2SmIE NN O

@BeFit4Llfe NN O
My NNP O
talents VB O
http//tco/Hg8zRRZMzV NN O
@jamieallisonnnn JJ O

@marinasgrapes JJ B-PER
@DeathByFroot JJ B-PER
OH NNP O
MY@FUCKING NNP O
GOD NNP O
HES NNP O
SUCH NNP O
A DT O
LITTTLE NNP O
BITCH NNP O
I PRP O
CANT VB O
BREATHE NNP O

I PRP O
miss NN O
my NN O
bestfriend NN O
😩😩😩 JJ O
@country_accent JJ O

Dwight NNP B-PER
Howard NNP I-PER
still JJ O
playing NN O
with NN O
no NNS O
focus JJ O
concentration NNS O
or NN O
energy NN O
Does NNP O
he NN O
realize NN O
these NN O
games VB O
aren't DT O
exhibition NN O
#Rockets # B-ORG
#Rednation # O

Tomorrow NNP O
my NN O
birthday NN O
😁👑 NN O

I PRP O
feel JJ O
like NN O
I PRP O
get NN O
fatter VB O
and DT O
fatter VB O
everyday NN O

First NNP O
night NN O
sleeping NN O
without NN O
Madi NNP B-PER

Lmao NNP O
I PRP O
love NN O
her NN O
💖 NN O
http//tco/CxGuKmaTGq NN O

Facetiming NNP O
with NN O
my NN O
mains VB O
back VB O
home NN O
16 CD O
days VB O
kitty's NN O
http//tco/MFpUBU5aCY NN O

What NNP O
tf NN O
am DT O
I PRP O
even NN O
watching VB O

About DT O
to NN O
watch VB O
The NNP B-MISC
Interview PRP I-MISC
with NN O
my NN O
legal NN O
guardians NN O

Lil NNP B-PER
boy NN O
how NN O
do NN O
u NN O
manage VB O
to NN O
cook NNS O
all DT O
of NN O
it NN O
Man NNP O
kiss NN O
it NN O
Keep NNP O
It PRP O
Simple NNP O
Stupid NNP O

pops NN O
a DT O
bottle NN O
won't NN O
close NNS O
it NN O

@rachelmlking NN B-PER
I PRP O
made VB O
mine NN O
suffer NN O
lol NN O
😩😩😂😂 JJ O
and DT O
then NN O
dove NN O
in NN O
for NN O
the NN O
final NN O
attack DT O

I PRP O
Hate NNP O
Being NNP O
Ignored PRP O
Yoo NNP O
Fr NNP O

I PRP O
like NN O
being NN O
her NN O
friend JJ O
sometimes NN O
😩😇 NN O
http//tco/cwt75SYFxB NN O

@HeartBreakSteez NN B-PER
on NN O
a DT O
females JJ O
part NN O
I PRP O
love NN O
to NN O
watch VB O
a DT O
dude NN O
suffer NN O
😈 NN O

@BASEDLIGHTSKlN NN B-PER
@littlemunecaa JJ B-PER
aw DT O
you NN O
made VB O
him NN O
use JJ O
that NN O
sad VB O
emoji NN O
😭😭 NN O

@Essaajules JJ B-PER
@RaymondSaysHi NN B-PER
LMAO NNP O
mr NN O
Steal NNP O
ya NN O
girl NN O
😂😂😂😂 JJ O

@ShesNicks JJ B-PER
@nascarGypz NN B-PER
@JackieFry JJ B-PER
@NiceCarGirl48 JJ B-PER
@Jodigirl48 JJ B-PER
@netter48 JJ B-PER
2 CD O
electric NN O
men NN O
gotta NN O
love NN O
it NN O

I'm PRP O
at DT O
Starbucks NNP B-ORG
in NN O
Virginia NNP B-LOC
Beach NNP I-LOC
VA VB I-LOC
https//tco/XDhAgmzQxk NN O

who NN O
wants VB O
that NN O
perfect NN O
love NN O
story NN O
anyway DT O

@cshueyy JJ B-PER
@saskhab NN B-PER
@colettetown JJ B-PER
van NN B-LOC
isle NN I-LOC
= NN O
not JJ O
shitty NN O

Old NNP O
man VB O
Winter NNP O
said VB O
he NN O
coming NNS O
in NN O
like NN O
a DT O
wrecking NN O
ball VB O
today NN O
That NNP O
Wind NNP O
is NN O
whippin NN O
son NN O
#Turnt # O

@steffoff JJ O
http//tco/uG0Pjq8sDC NN O

👀 NN O
RT NNP O
@Call_Me_Jadii JJ B-PER
@PoloAltJordan JJ B-PER
I'm PRP O
opening JJ O
it NN O
for NN O
you NN O
on NN O
my NN O
snapchat NN B-ORG
daddy VB O
😍😏 NN O

if NN O
you NN O
still JJ O
call VB O
me NN O
'tori' POS O
after DT O
i NN O
have VB O
asked DT O
to NN O
call VB O
me NN O
'victoria' POS O
multiple NN O
times NN O
the NN O
amount DT O
of NN O
respect NN O
you NN O
have VB O
for NN O
me NN O
is NN O
non-existent JJ O

22 CD O
Heartbreaking NNP O
Cartoons VB O
From NNP O
Artists DT O
Responding NNP O
To NNP O
The NNP O
Charlie NNP B-ORG
Hebdo NNP I-ORG
Shooting NNP O
- : O
http//tco/btqA4TcYRB NN O
#jesuischarlie # O

all DT O
i NN O
wanna VB O
do NN O
in NN O
this NN O
life NN O
is NN O
eat VB O
good NN O
WE NNP O
HUNGRY NNP O
🙏 NN O
http//tco/osp31ql1xW NN O

@PumaPamf JJ B-PER

@pattydangs4 NN B-PER
Thank NNP O
you😁 NN O

Lying NNP O
has VB O
been NN O
the NN O
one JJ O
single NN O
thing NN O
I'd PRP O
never JJ O
tolerate NN O
Nor NNP O
do NN O
i NN O
Main NNP O
thing NN O
me NN O
and DT O
my NN O
moms NN O
relationship NN O
thrived NN O
on NN O

@Nate_HH NN B-PER
You NNP O
bet NN O
Thanks NNP O
for NN O
the NN O
follow JJ O
back VB O
Be NNP O
sure NN O
to NN O
keep NN O
@ThomasG_WX JJ B-PER
in NN O
line NN O

the NN O
tampon VB O
loosie NN O
is NN O
the NN O
true NN O
untapped JJ O
market NN O

Dominos NNP B-PER
hurry NN O
up JJ O
😥 NN O

@maeve_riordan JJ B-PER
thx😊 NN O

Dying NNP O
my NN O
hair NN O
by NN O
myself NN O
is NN O
always DT O
a DT O
god NN O
damn VB O
disaster NN O
😂😂😂😂😂 JJ O

@drake NN B-PER
is NN O
a DT O
very NN O
nice NN O
looking NN O
individual NN O

@moneymanmiles_ JJ B-PER
ugh JJ O
no NNS O
my NN O
mama VB O
keep NN O
telling NN O
me NN O
to NN O
go NN O
there NN O
I'm PRP O
going NN O
to NN O
harper NN O
woods NN O

Getting NNP O
stitches JJ O
off JJ O
in NN O
2 CD O
days VB O
🎉🎉👍 JJ O

I PRP O
loved NN O
you NN O
more NN O
than NN O
ever NN O
more NN O
then NN O
my NN O
own JJ O
life NN O
